<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>California Weekly Pulse</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on California Weekly Pulse</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 17 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description>The California Weekly Pulse site was created and is maintained by the Stanford Data Lab. If you have any feedback, comments, or suggestions for improvements to this site, please email us.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Alameda County</title>
      <link>/alameda/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/alameda/</guid>
      <description>Food insecurity Unemployment   Food insecurity These food insecurity estimates for Alameda County’ are based upon a model. The model uses the food insecurity rate for the entire state and the county unemployment rates to estimate food insecurity for each county.
County unemployment rates are updated every month, but state-level food insecurity is updated every week. Each month’s unemployment data also comes out later than the food insecurity data.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Alpine County</title>
      <link>/alpine/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/alpine/</guid>
      <description>Food insecurity Unemployment   Food insecurity These food insecurity estimates for Alpine County’ are based upon a model. The model uses the food insecurity rate for the entire state and the county unemployment rates to estimate food insecurity for each county.
County unemployment rates are updated every month, but state-level food insecurity is updated every week. Each month’s unemployment data also comes out later than the food insecurity data.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Amador County</title>
      <link>/amador/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/amador/</guid>
      <description>Food insecurity Unemployment   Food insecurity These food insecurity estimates for Amador County’ are based upon a model. The model uses the food insecurity rate for the entire state and the county unemployment rates to estimate food insecurity for each county.
County unemployment rates are updated every month, but state-level food insecurity is updated every week. Each month’s unemployment data also comes out later than the food insecurity data.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Butte County</title>
      <link>/butte/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/butte/</guid>
      <description>Food insecurity Unemployment   Food insecurity These food insecurity estimates for Butte County’ are based upon a model. The model uses the food insecurity rate for the entire state and the county unemployment rates to estimate food insecurity for each county.
County unemployment rates are updated every month, but state-level food insecurity is updated every week. Each month’s unemployment data also comes out later than the food insecurity data.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Calaveras County</title>
      <link>/calaveras/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/calaveras/</guid>
      <description>Food insecurity Unemployment   Food insecurity These food insecurity estimates for Calaveras County’ are based upon a model. The model uses the food insecurity rate for the entire state and the county unemployment rates to estimate food insecurity for each county.
County unemployment rates are updated every month, but state-level food insecurity is updated every week. Each month’s unemployment data also comes out later than the food insecurity data.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>California</title>
      <link>/state/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/state/</guid>
      <description>Overview Food insecurity Unemployment   Overview The data on this site is derived from the U.S. Census Bureau Household Pulse Survey (HPS) and the U.S. Bureau of Labor Statistics Local Area Unemployment Statistics (LAUS). New HPS data is released once a week, and new LAUS data is released once a month. The most recent data used for this report are:
 Household Pulse Survey: May 28 - June 2 Local Area Unemployment Statistics: April  The HPS releases data in two stages.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Colusa County</title>
      <link>/colusa/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/colusa/</guid>
      <description>Food insecurity Unemployment   Food insecurity These food insecurity estimates for Colusa County’ are based upon a model. The model uses the food insecurity rate for the entire state and the county unemployment rates to estimate food insecurity for each county.
County unemployment rates are updated every month, but state-level food insecurity is updated every week. Each month’s unemployment data also comes out later than the food insecurity data.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contra Costa County</title>
      <link>/contra-costa/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/contra-costa/</guid>
      <description>Food insecurity Unemployment   Food insecurity These food insecurity estimates for Contra Costa County’ are based upon a model. The model uses the food insecurity rate for the entire state and the county unemployment rates to estimate food insecurity for each county.
County unemployment rates are updated every month, but state-level food insecurity is updated every week. Each month’s unemployment data also comes out later than the food insecurity data.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Del Norte County</title>
      <link>/del-norte/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/del-norte/</guid>
      <description>Food insecurity Unemployment   Food insecurity These food insecurity estimates for Del Norte County’ are based upon a model. The model uses the food insecurity rate for the entire state and the county unemployment rates to estimate food insecurity for each county.
County unemployment rates are updated every month, but state-level food insecurity is updated every week. Each month’s unemployment data also comes out later than the food insecurity data.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>El Dorado County</title>
      <link>/el-dorado/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/el-dorado/</guid>
      <description>Food insecurity Unemployment   Food insecurity These food insecurity estimates for El Dorado County’ are based upon a model. The model uses the food insecurity rate for the entire state and the county unemployment rates to estimate food insecurity for each county.
County unemployment rates are updated every month, but state-level food insecurity is updated every week. Each month’s unemployment data also comes out later than the food insecurity data.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fresno County</title>
      <link>/fresno/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/fresno/</guid>
      <description>Food insecurity Unemployment   Food insecurity These food insecurity estimates for Fresno County’ are based upon a model. The model uses the food insecurity rate for the entire state and the county unemployment rates to estimate food insecurity for each county.
County unemployment rates are updated every month, but state-level food insecurity is updated every week. Each month’s unemployment data also comes out later than the food insecurity data.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Glenn County</title>
      <link>/glenn/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/glenn/</guid>
      <description>Food insecurity Unemployment   Food insecurity These food insecurity estimates for Glenn County’ are based upon a model. The model uses the food insecurity rate for the entire state and the county unemployment rates to estimate food insecurity for each county.
County unemployment rates are updated every month, but state-level food insecurity is updated every week. Each month’s unemployment data also comes out later than the food insecurity data.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Humboldt County</title>
      <link>/humboldt/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/humboldt/</guid>
      <description>Food insecurity Unemployment   Food insecurity These food insecurity estimates for Humboldt County’ are based upon a model. The model uses the food insecurity rate for the entire state and the county unemployment rates to estimate food insecurity for each county.
County unemployment rates are updated every month, but state-level food insecurity is updated every week. Each month’s unemployment data also comes out later than the food insecurity data.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Imperial County</title>
      <link>/imperial/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/imperial/</guid>
      <description>Food insecurity Unemployment   Food insecurity These food insecurity estimates for Imperial County’ are based upon a model. The model uses the food insecurity rate for the entire state and the county unemployment rates to estimate food insecurity for each county.
County unemployment rates are updated every month, but state-level food insecurity is updated every week. Each month’s unemployment data also comes out later than the food insecurity data.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Inyo County</title>
      <link>/inyo/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/inyo/</guid>
      <description>Food insecurity Unemployment   Food insecurity These food insecurity estimates for Inyo County’ are based upon a model. The model uses the food insecurity rate for the entire state and the county unemployment rates to estimate food insecurity for each county.
County unemployment rates are updated every month, but state-level food insecurity is updated every week. Each month’s unemployment data also comes out later than the food insecurity data.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kern County</title>
      <link>/kern/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/kern/</guid>
      <description>Food insecurity Unemployment   Food insecurity These food insecurity estimates for Kern County’ are based upon a model. The model uses the food insecurity rate for the entire state and the county unemployment rates to estimate food insecurity for each county.
County unemployment rates are updated every month, but state-level food insecurity is updated every week. Each month’s unemployment data also comes out later than the food insecurity data.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kings County</title>
      <link>/kings/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/kings/</guid>
      <description>Food insecurity Unemployment   Food insecurity These food insecurity estimates for Kings County’ are based upon a model. The model uses the food insecurity rate for the entire state and the county unemployment rates to estimate food insecurity for each county.
County unemployment rates are updated every month, but state-level food insecurity is updated every week. Each month’s unemployment data also comes out later than the food insecurity data.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lake County</title>
      <link>/lake/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/lake/</guid>
      <description>Food insecurity Unemployment   Food insecurity These food insecurity estimates for Lake County’ are based upon a model. The model uses the food insecurity rate for the entire state and the county unemployment rates to estimate food insecurity for each county.
County unemployment rates are updated every month, but state-level food insecurity is updated every week. Each month’s unemployment data also comes out later than the food insecurity data.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lassen County</title>
      <link>/lassen/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/lassen/</guid>
      <description>Food insecurity Unemployment   Food insecurity These food insecurity estimates for Lassen County’ are based upon a model. The model uses the food insecurity rate for the entire state and the county unemployment rates to estimate food insecurity for each county.
County unemployment rates are updated every month, but state-level food insecurity is updated every week. Each month’s unemployment data also comes out later than the food insecurity data.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Los Angeles County</title>
      <link>/los-angeles/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/los-angeles/</guid>
      <description>Food insecurity Unemployment   Food insecurity These food insecurity estimates for Los Angeles County’ are based upon a model. The model uses the food insecurity rate for the entire state and the county unemployment rates to estimate food insecurity for each county.
County unemployment rates are updated every month, but state-level food insecurity is updated every week. Each month’s unemployment data also comes out later than the food insecurity data.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Madera County</title>
      <link>/madera/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/madera/</guid>
      <description>Food insecurity Unemployment   Food insecurity These food insecurity estimates for Madera County’ are based upon a model. The model uses the food insecurity rate for the entire state and the county unemployment rates to estimate food insecurity for each county.
County unemployment rates are updated every month, but state-level food insecurity is updated every week. Each month’s unemployment data also comes out later than the food insecurity data.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Marin County</title>
      <link>/marin/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/marin/</guid>
      <description>Food insecurity Unemployment   Food insecurity These food insecurity estimates for Marin County’ are based upon a model. The model uses the food insecurity rate for the entire state and the county unemployment rates to estimate food insecurity for each county.
County unemployment rates are updated every month, but state-level food insecurity is updated every week. Each month’s unemployment data also comes out later than the food insecurity data.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mariposa County</title>
      <link>/mariposa/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/mariposa/</guid>
      <description>Food insecurity Unemployment   Food insecurity These food insecurity estimates for Mariposa County’ are based upon a model. The model uses the food insecurity rate for the entire state and the county unemployment rates to estimate food insecurity for each county.
County unemployment rates are updated every month, but state-level food insecurity is updated every week. Each month’s unemployment data also comes out later than the food insecurity data.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mendocino County</title>
      <link>/mendocino/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/mendocino/</guid>
      <description>Food insecurity Unemployment   Food insecurity These food insecurity estimates for Mendocino County’ are based upon a model. The model uses the food insecurity rate for the entire state and the county unemployment rates to estimate food insecurity for each county.
County unemployment rates are updated every month, but state-level food insecurity is updated every week. Each month’s unemployment data also comes out later than the food insecurity data.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Merced County</title>
      <link>/merced/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/merced/</guid>
      <description>Food insecurity Unemployment   Food insecurity These food insecurity estimates for Merced County’ are based upon a model. The model uses the food insecurity rate for the entire state and the county unemployment rates to estimate food insecurity for each county.
County unemployment rates are updated every month, but state-level food insecurity is updated every week. Each month’s unemployment data also comes out later than the food insecurity data.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Modoc County</title>
      <link>/modoc/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/modoc/</guid>
      <description>Food insecurity Unemployment   Food insecurity These food insecurity estimates for Modoc County’ are based upon a model. The model uses the food insecurity rate for the entire state and the county unemployment rates to estimate food insecurity for each county.
County unemployment rates are updated every month, but state-level food insecurity is updated every week. Each month’s unemployment data also comes out later than the food insecurity data.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mono County</title>
      <link>/mono/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/mono/</guid>
      <description>Food insecurity Unemployment   Food insecurity These food insecurity estimates for Mono County’ are based upon a model. The model uses the food insecurity rate for the entire state and the county unemployment rates to estimate food insecurity for each county.
County unemployment rates are updated every month, but state-level food insecurity is updated every week. Each month’s unemployment data also comes out later than the food insecurity data.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Monterey County</title>
      <link>/monterey/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/monterey/</guid>
      <description>Food insecurity Unemployment   Food insecurity These food insecurity estimates for Monterey County’ are based upon a model. The model uses the food insecurity rate for the entire state and the county unemployment rates to estimate food insecurity for each county.
County unemployment rates are updated every month, but state-level food insecurity is updated every week. Each month’s unemployment data also comes out later than the food insecurity data.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Napa County</title>
      <link>/napa/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/napa/</guid>
      <description>Food insecurity Unemployment   Food insecurity These food insecurity estimates for Napa County’ are based upon a model. The model uses the food insecurity rate for the entire state and the county unemployment rates to estimate food insecurity for each county.
County unemployment rates are updated every month, but state-level food insecurity is updated every week. Each month’s unemployment data also comes out later than the food insecurity data.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nevada County</title>
      <link>/nevada/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/nevada/</guid>
      <description>Food insecurity Unemployment   Food insecurity These food insecurity estimates for Nevada County’ are based upon a model. The model uses the food insecurity rate for the entire state and the county unemployment rates to estimate food insecurity for each county.
County unemployment rates are updated every month, but state-level food insecurity is updated every week. Each month’s unemployment data also comes out later than the food insecurity data.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Orange County</title>
      <link>/orange/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/orange/</guid>
      <description>Food insecurity Unemployment   Food insecurity These food insecurity estimates for Orange County’ are based upon a model. The model uses the food insecurity rate for the entire state and the county unemployment rates to estimate food insecurity for each county.
County unemployment rates are updated every month, but state-level food insecurity is updated every week. Each month’s unemployment data also comes out later than the food insecurity data.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Placer County</title>
      <link>/placer/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/placer/</guid>
      <description>Food insecurity Unemployment   Food insecurity These food insecurity estimates for Placer County’ are based upon a model. The model uses the food insecurity rate for the entire state and the county unemployment rates to estimate food insecurity for each county.
County unemployment rates are updated every month, but state-level food insecurity is updated every week. Each month’s unemployment data also comes out later than the food insecurity data.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Plumas County</title>
      <link>/plumas/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/plumas/</guid>
      <description>Food insecurity Unemployment   Food insecurity These food insecurity estimates for Plumas County’ are based upon a model. The model uses the food insecurity rate for the entire state and the county unemployment rates to estimate food insecurity for each county.
County unemployment rates are updated every month, but state-level food insecurity is updated every week. Each month’s unemployment data also comes out later than the food insecurity data.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Riverside County</title>
      <link>/riverside/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/riverside/</guid>
      <description>Food insecurity Unemployment   Food insecurity These food insecurity estimates for Riverside County’ are based upon a model. The model uses the food insecurity rate for the entire state and the county unemployment rates to estimate food insecurity for each county.
County unemployment rates are updated every month, but state-level food insecurity is updated every week. Each month’s unemployment data also comes out later than the food insecurity data.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sacramento County</title>
      <link>/sacramento/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/sacramento/</guid>
      <description>Food insecurity Unemployment   Food insecurity These food insecurity estimates for Sacramento County’ are based upon a model. The model uses the food insecurity rate for the entire state and the county unemployment rates to estimate food insecurity for each county.
County unemployment rates are updated every month, but state-level food insecurity is updated every week. Each month’s unemployment data also comes out later than the food insecurity data.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>San Benito County</title>
      <link>/san-benito/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/san-benito/</guid>
      <description>Food insecurity Unemployment   Food insecurity These food insecurity estimates for San Benito County’ are based upon a model. The model uses the food insecurity rate for the entire state and the county unemployment rates to estimate food insecurity for each county.
County unemployment rates are updated every month, but state-level food insecurity is updated every week. Each month’s unemployment data also comes out later than the food insecurity data.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>San Bernardino County</title>
      <link>/san-bernardino/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/san-bernardino/</guid>
      <description>Food insecurity Unemployment   Food insecurity These food insecurity estimates for San Bernardino County’ are based upon a model. The model uses the food insecurity rate for the entire state and the county unemployment rates to estimate food insecurity for each county.
County unemployment rates are updated every month, but state-level food insecurity is updated every week. Each month’s unemployment data also comes out later than the food insecurity data.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>San Diego County</title>
      <link>/san-diego/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/san-diego/</guid>
      <description>Food insecurity Unemployment   Food insecurity These food insecurity estimates for San Diego County’ are based upon a model. The model uses the food insecurity rate for the entire state and the county unemployment rates to estimate food insecurity for each county.
County unemployment rates are updated every month, but state-level food insecurity is updated every week. Each month’s unemployment data also comes out later than the food insecurity data.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>San Francisco County</title>
      <link>/san-francisco/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/san-francisco/</guid>
      <description>Food insecurity Unemployment   Food insecurity These food insecurity estimates for San Francisco County’ are based upon a model. The model uses the food insecurity rate for the entire state and the county unemployment rates to estimate food insecurity for each county.
County unemployment rates are updated every month, but state-level food insecurity is updated every week. Each month’s unemployment data also comes out later than the food insecurity data.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>San Joaquin County</title>
      <link>/san-joaquin/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/san-joaquin/</guid>
      <description>Food insecurity Unemployment   Food insecurity These food insecurity estimates for San Joaquin County’ are based upon a model. The model uses the food insecurity rate for the entire state and the county unemployment rates to estimate food insecurity for each county.
County unemployment rates are updated every month, but state-level food insecurity is updated every week. Each month’s unemployment data also comes out later than the food insecurity data.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>San Luis Obispo County</title>
      <link>/san-luis-obispo/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/san-luis-obispo/</guid>
      <description>Food insecurity Unemployment   Food insecurity These food insecurity estimates for San Luis Obispo County’ are based upon a model. The model uses the food insecurity rate for the entire state and the county unemployment rates to estimate food insecurity for each county.
County unemployment rates are updated every month, but state-level food insecurity is updated every week. Each month’s unemployment data also comes out later than the food insecurity data.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>San Mateo County</title>
      <link>/san-mateo/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/san-mateo/</guid>
      <description>Food insecurity Unemployment   Food insecurity These food insecurity estimates for San Mateo County’ are based upon a model. The model uses the food insecurity rate for the entire state and the county unemployment rates to estimate food insecurity for each county.
County unemployment rates are updated every month, but state-level food insecurity is updated every week. Each month’s unemployment data also comes out later than the food insecurity data.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Santa Barbara County</title>
      <link>/santa-barbara/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/santa-barbara/</guid>
      <description>Food insecurity Unemployment   Food insecurity These food insecurity estimates for Santa Barbara County’ are based upon a model. The model uses the food insecurity rate for the entire state and the county unemployment rates to estimate food insecurity for each county.
County unemployment rates are updated every month, but state-level food insecurity is updated every week. Each month’s unemployment data also comes out later than the food insecurity data.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Santa Clara County</title>
      <link>/santa-clara/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/santa-clara/</guid>
      <description>Food insecurity Unemployment   Food insecurity These food insecurity estimates for Santa Clara County’ are based upon a model. The model uses the food insecurity rate for the entire state and the county unemployment rates to estimate food insecurity for each county.
County unemployment rates are updated every month, but state-level food insecurity is updated every week. Each month’s unemployment data also comes out later than the food insecurity data.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Santa Cruz County</title>
      <link>/santa-cruz/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/santa-cruz/</guid>
      <description>Food insecurity Unemployment   Food insecurity These food insecurity estimates for Santa Cruz County’ are based upon a model. The model uses the food insecurity rate for the entire state and the county unemployment rates to estimate food insecurity for each county.
County unemployment rates are updated every month, but state-level food insecurity is updated every week. Each month’s unemployment data also comes out later than the food insecurity data.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shasta County</title>
      <link>/shasta/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/shasta/</guid>
      <description>Food insecurity Unemployment   Food insecurity These food insecurity estimates for Shasta County’ are based upon a model. The model uses the food insecurity rate for the entire state and the county unemployment rates to estimate food insecurity for each county.
County unemployment rates are updated every month, but state-level food insecurity is updated every week. Each month’s unemployment data also comes out later than the food insecurity data.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sierra County</title>
      <link>/sierra/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/sierra/</guid>
      <description>Food insecurity Unemployment   Food insecurity These food insecurity estimates for Sierra County’ are based upon a model. The model uses the food insecurity rate for the entire state and the county unemployment rates to estimate food insecurity for each county.
County unemployment rates are updated every month, but state-level food insecurity is updated every week. Each month’s unemployment data also comes out later than the food insecurity data.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Siskiyou County</title>
      <link>/siskiyou/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/siskiyou/</guid>
      <description>Food insecurity Unemployment   Food insecurity These food insecurity estimates for Siskiyou County’ are based upon a model. The model uses the food insecurity rate for the entire state and the county unemployment rates to estimate food insecurity for each county.
County unemployment rates are updated every month, but state-level food insecurity is updated every week. Each month’s unemployment data also comes out later than the food insecurity data.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Solano County</title>
      <link>/solano/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/solano/</guid>
      <description>Food insecurity Unemployment   Food insecurity These food insecurity estimates for Solano County’ are based upon a model. The model uses the food insecurity rate for the entire state and the county unemployment rates to estimate food insecurity for each county.
County unemployment rates are updated every month, but state-level food insecurity is updated every week. Each month’s unemployment data also comes out later than the food insecurity data.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sonoma County</title>
      <link>/sonoma/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/sonoma/</guid>
      <description>Food insecurity Unemployment   Food insecurity These food insecurity estimates for Sonoma County’ are based upon a model. The model uses the food insecurity rate for the entire state and the county unemployment rates to estimate food insecurity for each county.
County unemployment rates are updated every month, but state-level food insecurity is updated every week. Each month’s unemployment data also comes out later than the food insecurity data.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stanislaus County</title>
      <link>/stanislaus/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stanislaus/</guid>
      <description>Food insecurity Unemployment   Food insecurity These food insecurity estimates for Stanislaus County’ are based upon a model. The model uses the food insecurity rate for the entire state and the county unemployment rates to estimate food insecurity for each county.
County unemployment rates are updated every month, but state-level food insecurity is updated every week. Each month’s unemployment data also comes out later than the food insecurity data.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sutter County</title>
      <link>/sutter/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/sutter/</guid>
      <description>Food insecurity Unemployment   Food insecurity These food insecurity estimates for Sutter County’ are based upon a model. The model uses the food insecurity rate for the entire state and the county unemployment rates to estimate food insecurity for each county.
County unemployment rates are updated every month, but state-level food insecurity is updated every week. Each month’s unemployment data also comes out later than the food insecurity data.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tehama County</title>
      <link>/tehama/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/tehama/</guid>
      <description>Food insecurity Unemployment   Food insecurity These food insecurity estimates for Tehama County’ are based upon a model. The model uses the food insecurity rate for the entire state and the county unemployment rates to estimate food insecurity for each county.
County unemployment rates are updated every month, but state-level food insecurity is updated every week. Each month’s unemployment data also comes out later than the food insecurity data.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Trinity County</title>
      <link>/trinity/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/trinity/</guid>
      <description>Food insecurity Unemployment   Food insecurity These food insecurity estimates for Trinity County’ are based upon a model. The model uses the food insecurity rate for the entire state and the county unemployment rates to estimate food insecurity for each county.
County unemployment rates are updated every month, but state-level food insecurity is updated every week. Each month’s unemployment data also comes out later than the food insecurity data.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tulare County</title>
      <link>/tulare/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/tulare/</guid>
      <description>Food insecurity Unemployment   Food insecurity These food insecurity estimates for Tulare County’ are based upon a model. The model uses the food insecurity rate for the entire state and the county unemployment rates to estimate food insecurity for each county.
County unemployment rates are updated every month, but state-level food insecurity is updated every week. Each month’s unemployment data also comes out later than the food insecurity data.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tuolumne County</title>
      <link>/tuolumne/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/tuolumne/</guid>
      <description>Food insecurity Unemployment   Food insecurity These food insecurity estimates for Tuolumne County’ are based upon a model. The model uses the food insecurity rate for the entire state and the county unemployment rates to estimate food insecurity for each county.
County unemployment rates are updated every month, but state-level food insecurity is updated every week. Each month’s unemployment data also comes out later than the food insecurity data.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ventura County</title>
      <link>/ventura/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/ventura/</guid>
      <description>Food insecurity Unemployment   Food insecurity These food insecurity estimates for Ventura County’ are based upon a model. The model uses the food insecurity rate for the entire state and the county unemployment rates to estimate food insecurity for each county.
County unemployment rates are updated every month, but state-level food insecurity is updated every week. Each month’s unemployment data also comes out later than the food insecurity data.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Yolo County</title>
      <link>/yolo/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/yolo/</guid>
      <description>Food insecurity Unemployment   Food insecurity These food insecurity estimates for Yolo County’ are based upon a model. The model uses the food insecurity rate for the entire state and the county unemployment rates to estimate food insecurity for each county.
County unemployment rates are updated every month, but state-level food insecurity is updated every week. Each month’s unemployment data also comes out later than the food insecurity data.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Yuba County</title>
      <link>/yuba/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/yuba/</guid>
      <description>Food insecurity Unemployment   Food insecurity These food insecurity estimates for Yuba County’ are based upon a model. The model uses the food insecurity rate for the entire state and the county unemployment rates to estimate food insecurity for each county.
County unemployment rates are updated every month, but state-level food insecurity is updated every week. Each month’s unemployment data also comes out later than the food insecurity data.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>