<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>California Pulse</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on California Pulse</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description>The California Weekly Pulse site was created and is maintained by the Stanford Data Lab. If you have any feedback, comments, or suggestions for improvements to this site, please email us.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Alameda County</title>
      <link>/alameda/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/alameda/</guid>
      <description>Food insufficiency Unemployment Food insufficiency In the most recent survey period that ended September 26, an estimated 8.6% of Alameda County adults, or approximately 98,400 adults, lived in households experiencing food insufficiency.
Using a model based upon data from the Food Security Supplement of the Current Population Survey, we estimate that in the most recent survey period, 7.7% of children, or approximately 25,500 children, experienced food insufficiency.
Because the Household Pulse Survey does not provide data at the county level, we use a model to estimate county-level food insufficiency.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Alpine County</title>
      <link>/alpine/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/alpine/</guid>
      <description>Food insufficiency Unemployment Food insufficiency In the most recent survey period that ended September 26, an estimated 12.3% of Alpine County adults, or approximately 98 adults, lived in households experiencing food insufficiency.
Using a model based upon data from the Food Security Supplement of the Current Population Survey, we estimate that in the most recent survey period, 10.3% of children, or approximately 20 children, experienced food insufficiency.
Because the Household Pulse Survey does not provide data at the county level, we use a model to estimate county-level food insufficiency.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Amador County</title>
      <link>/amador/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/amador/</guid>
      <description>Food insufficiency Unemployment Food insufficiency In the most recent survey period that ended September 26, an estimated 7.6% of Amador County adults, or approximately 2,210 adults, lived in households experiencing food insufficiency.
Using a model based upon data from the Food Security Supplement of the Current Population Survey, we estimate that in the most recent survey period, 7.0% of children, or approximately 409 children, experienced food insufficiency.
Because the Household Pulse Survey does not provide data at the county level, we use a model to estimate county-level food insufficiency.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Butte County</title>
      <link>/butte/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/butte/</guid>
      <description>Food insufficiency Unemployment Food insufficiency In the most recent survey period that ended September 26, an estimated 9.7% of Butte County adults, or approximately 14,400 adults, lived in households experiencing food insufficiency.
Using a model based upon data from the Food Security Supplement of the Current Population Survey, we estimate that in the most recent survey period, 8.4% of children, or approximately 3,640 children, experienced food insufficiency.
Because the Household Pulse Survey does not provide data at the county level, we use a model to estimate county-level food insufficiency.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Calaveras County</title>
      <link>/calaveras/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/calaveras/</guid>
      <description>Food insufficiency Unemployment Food insufficiency In the most recent survey period that ended September 26, an estimated 8.2% of Calaveras County adults, or approximately 2,680 adults, lived in households experiencing food insufficiency.
Using a model based upon data from the Food Security Supplement of the Current Population Survey, we estimate that in the most recent survey period, 7.4% of children, or approximately 564 children, experienced food insufficiency.
Because the Household Pulse Survey does not provide data at the county level, we use a model to estimate county-level food insufficiency.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>California</title>
      <link>/state/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/state/</guid>
      <description>Overview Food insufficiency Rate over time Geography Demographics Reasons Severity Supplemental Nutrition Assitance Program (SNAP) Free groceries Unemployment Rate over time Geography Unemployment and food insufficiency Overview The data on this site is derived from the U.S. Census Bureau Household Pulse Survey (HPS) and the U.S. Bureau of Labor Statistics Local Area Unemployment Statistics (LAUS). New HPS data is currently released every four weeks, and new LAUS data is released once a month.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Colusa County</title>
      <link>/colusa/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/colusa/</guid>
      <description>Food insufficiency Unemployment Food insufficiency In the most recent survey period that ended September 26, an estimated 24.7% of Colusa County adults, or approximately 3,320 adults, lived in households experiencing food insufficiency.
Using a model based upon data from the Food Security Supplement of the Current Population Survey, we estimate that in the most recent survey period, 19.0% of children, or approximately 1,080 children, experienced food insufficiency.
Because the Household Pulse Survey does not provide data at the county level, we use a model to estimate county-level food insufficiency.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contra Costa County</title>
      <link>/contra-costa/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/contra-costa/</guid>
      <description>Food insufficiency Unemployment Food insufficiency In the most recent survey period that ended September 26, an estimated 9.2% of Contra Costa County adults, or approximately 70,300 adults, lived in households experiencing food insufficiency.
Using a model based upon data from the Food Security Supplement of the Current Population Survey, we estimate that in the most recent survey period, 8.0% of children, or approximately 20,300 children, experienced food insufficiency.
Because the Household Pulse Survey does not provide data at the county level, we use a model to estimate county-level food insufficiency.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Del Norte County</title>
      <link>/del-norte/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/del-norte/</guid>
      <description>Food insufficiency Unemployment Food insufficiency In the most recent survey period that ended September 26, an estimated 9.1% of Del Norte County adults, or approximately 1,700 adults, lived in households experiencing food insufficiency.
Using a model based upon data from the Food Security Supplement of the Current Population Survey, we estimate that in the most recent survey period, 8.0% of children, or approximately 453 children, experienced food insufficiency.
Because the Household Pulse Survey does not provide data at the county level, we use a model to estimate county-level food insufficiency.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>El Dorado County</title>
      <link>/el-dorado/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/el-dorado/</guid>
      <description>Food insufficiency Unemployment Food insufficiency In the most recent survey period that ended September 26, an estimated 7.9% of El Dorado County adults, or approximately 10,500 adults, lived in households experiencing food insufficiency.
Using a model based upon data from the Food Security Supplement of the Current Population Survey, we estimate that in the most recent survey period, 7.2% of children, or approximately 2,660 children, experienced food insufficiency.
Because the Household Pulse Survey does not provide data at the county level, we use a model to estimate county-level food insufficiency.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fresno County</title>
      <link>/fresno/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/fresno/</guid>
      <description>Food insufficiency Unemployment Food insufficiency In the most recent survey period that ended September 26, an estimated 16.5% of Fresno County adults, or approximately 101,000 adults, lived in households experiencing food insufficiency.
Using a model based upon data from the Food Security Supplement of the Current Population Survey, we estimate that in the most recent survey period, 13.2% of children, or approximately 36,500 children, experienced food insufficiency.
Because the Household Pulse Survey does not provide data at the county level, we use a model to estimate county-level food insufficiency.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Glenn County</title>
      <link>/glenn/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/glenn/</guid>
      <description>Food insufficiency Unemployment Food insufficiency In the most recent survey period that ended September 26, an estimated 13.4% of Glenn County adults, or approximately 2,390 adults, lived in households experiencing food insufficiency.
Using a model based upon data from the Food Security Supplement of the Current Population Survey, we estimate that in the most recent survey period, 11.0% of children, or approximately 815 children, experienced food insufficiency.
Because the Household Pulse Survey does not provide data at the county level, we use a model to estimate county-level food insufficiency.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Humboldt County</title>
      <link>/humboldt/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/humboldt/</guid>
      <description>Food insufficiency Unemployment Food insufficiency In the most recent survey period that ended September 26, an estimated 8.9% of Humboldt County adults, or approximately 8,320 adults, lived in households experiencing food insufficiency.
Using a model based upon data from the Food Security Supplement of the Current Population Survey, we estimate that in the most recent survey period, 7.8% of children, or approximately 1,960 children, experienced food insufficiency.
Because the Household Pulse Survey does not provide data at the county level, we use a model to estimate county-level food insufficiency.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Imperial County</title>
      <link>/imperial/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/imperial/</guid>
      <description>Food insufficiency Unemployment Food insufficiency In the most recent survey period that ended September 26, an estimated 39.1% of Imperial County adults, or approximately 43,300 adults, lived in households experiencing food insufficiency.
Using a model based upon data from the Food Security Supplement of the Current Population Survey, we estimate that in the most recent survey period, 29.1% of children, or approximately 14,700 children, experienced food insufficiency.
Because the Household Pulse Survey does not provide data at the county level, we use a model to estimate county-level food insufficiency.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Inyo County</title>
      <link>/inyo/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/inyo/</guid>
      <description>Food insufficiency Unemployment Food insufficiency In the most recent survey period that ended September 26, an estimated 8.1% of Inyo County adults, or approximately 992 adults, lived in households experiencing food insufficiency.
Using a model based upon data from the Food Security Supplement of the Current Population Survey, we estimate that in the most recent survey period, 7.3% of children, or approximately 265 children, experienced food insufficiency.
Because the Household Pulse Survey does not provide data at the county level, we use a model to estimate county-level food insufficiency.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kern County</title>
      <link>/kern/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/kern/</guid>
      <description>Food insufficiency Unemployment Food insufficiency In the most recent survey period that ended September 26, an estimated 18.1% of Kern County adults, or approximately 99,400 adults, lived in households experiencing food insufficiency.
Using a model based upon data from the Food Security Supplement of the Current Population Survey, we estimate that in the most recent survey period, 14.4% of children, or approximately 36,400 children, experienced food insufficiency.
Because the Household Pulse Survey does not provide data at the county level, we use a model to estimate county-level food insufficiency.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kings County</title>
      <link>/kings/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/kings/</guid>
      <description>Food insufficiency Unemployment Food insufficiency In the most recent survey period that ended September 26, an estimated 14.0% of Kings County adults, or approximately 13,400 adults, lived in households experiencing food insufficiency.
Using a model based upon data from the Food Security Supplement of the Current Population Survey, we estimate that in the most recent survey period, 11.5% of children, or approximately 4,640 children, experienced food insufficiency.
Because the Household Pulse Survey does not provide data at the county level, we use a model to estimate county-level food insufficiency.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lake County</title>
      <link>/lake/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/lake/</guid>
      <description>Food insufficiency Unemployment Food insufficiency In the most recent survey period that ended September 26, an estimated 11.4% of Lake County adults, or approximately 4,960 adults, lived in households experiencing food insufficiency.
Using a model based upon data from the Food Security Supplement of the Current Population Survey, we estimate that in the most recent survey period, 9.6% of children, or approximately 1,280 children, experienced food insufficiency.
Because the Household Pulse Survey does not provide data at the county level, we use a model to estimate county-level food insufficiency.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lassen County</title>
      <link>/lassen/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/lassen/</guid>
      <description>Food insufficiency Unemployment Food insufficiency In the most recent survey period that ended September 26, an estimated 5.9% of Lassen County adults, or approximately 1,280 adults, lived in households experiencing food insufficiency.
Using a model based upon data from the Food Security Supplement of the Current Population Survey, we estimate that in the most recent survey period, 5.7% of children, or approximately 297 children, experienced food insufficiency.
Because the Household Pulse Survey does not provide data at the county level, we use a model to estimate county-level food insufficiency.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Los Angeles County</title>
      <link>/los-angeles/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/los-angeles/</guid>
      <description>Food insufficiency Unemployment Food insufficiency In the most recent survey period that ended September 26, an estimated 13.6% of Los Angeles County adults, or approximately 921,000 adults, lived in households experiencing food insufficiency.
Using a model based upon data from the Food Security Supplement of the Current Population Survey, we estimate that in the most recent survey period, 11.2% of children, or approximately 235,000 children, experienced food insufficiency.
Because the Household Pulse Survey does not provide data at the county level, we use a model to estimate county-level food insufficiency.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Madera County</title>
      <link>/madera/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/madera/</guid>
      <description>Food insufficiency Unemployment Food insufficiency In the most recent survey period that ended September 26, an estimated 13.7% of Madera County adults, or approximately 13,400 adults, lived in households experiencing food insufficiency.
Using a model based upon data from the Food Security Supplement of the Current Population Survey, we estimate that in the most recent survey period, 11.2% of children, or approximately 4,730 children, experienced food insufficiency.
Because the Household Pulse Survey does not provide data at the county level, we use a model to estimate county-level food insufficiency.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Marin County</title>
      <link>/marin/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/marin/</guid>
      <description>Food insufficiency Unemployment Food insufficiency In the most recent survey period that ended September 26, an estimated 6.6% of Marin County adults, or approximately 11,800 adults, lived in households experiencing food insufficiency.
Using a model based upon data from the Food Security Supplement of the Current Population Survey, we estimate that in the most recent survey period, 6.2% of children, or approximately 3,130 children, experienced food insufficiency.
Because the Household Pulse Survey does not provide data at the county level, we use a model to estimate county-level food insufficiency.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mariposa County</title>
      <link>/mariposa/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/mariposa/</guid>
      <description>Food insufficiency Unemployment Food insufficiency In the most recent survey period that ended September 26, an estimated 9.1% of Mariposa County adults, or approximately 1,120 adults, lived in households experiencing food insufficiency.
Using a model based upon data from the Food Security Supplement of the Current Population Survey, we estimate that in the most recent survey period, 8.0% of children, or approximately 217 children, experienced food insufficiency.
Because the Household Pulse Survey does not provide data at the county level, we use a model to estimate county-level food insufficiency.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mendocino County</title>
      <link>/mendocino/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/mendocino/</guid>
      <description>Food insufficiency Unemployment Food insufficiency In the most recent survey period that ended September 26, an estimated 8.6% of Mendocino County adults, or approximately 5,010 adults, lived in households experiencing food insufficiency.
Using a model based upon data from the Food Security Supplement of the Current Population Survey, we estimate that in the most recent survey period, 7.6% of children, or approximately 1,360 children, experienced food insufficiency.
Because the Household Pulse Survey does not provide data at the county level, we use a model to estimate county-level food insufficiency.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Merced County</title>
      <link>/merced/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/merced/</guid>
      <description>Food insufficiency Unemployment Food insufficiency In the most recent survey period that ended September 26, an estimated 17.9% of Merced County adults, or approximately 30,100 adults, lived in households experiencing food insufficiency.
Using a model based upon data from the Food Security Supplement of the Current Population Survey, we estimate that in the most recent survey period, 14.2% of children, or approximately 11,300 children, experienced food insufficiency.
Because the Household Pulse Survey does not provide data at the county level, we use a model to estimate county-level food insufficiency.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Modoc County</title>
      <link>/modoc/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/modoc/</guid>
      <description>Food insufficiency Unemployment Food insufficiency In the most recent survey period that ended September 26, an estimated 8.3% of Modoc County adults, or approximately 504 adults, lived in households experiencing food insufficiency.
Using a model based upon data from the Food Security Supplement of the Current Population Survey, we estimate that in the most recent survey period, 7.4% of children, or approximately 124 children, experienced food insufficiency.
Because the Household Pulse Survey does not provide data at the county level, we use a model to estimate county-level food insufficiency.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mono County</title>
      <link>/mono/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/mono/</guid>
      <description>Food insufficiency Unemployment Food insufficiency In the most recent survey period that ended September 26, an estimated 11.4% of Mono County adults, or approximately 1,160 adults, lived in households experiencing food insufficiency.
Using a model based upon data from the Food Security Supplement of the Current Population Survey, we estimate that in the most recent survey period, 9.6% of children, or approximately 242 children, experienced food insufficiency.
Because the Household Pulse Survey does not provide data at the county level, we use a model to estimate county-level food insufficiency.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Monterey County</title>
      <link>/monterey/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/monterey/</guid>
      <description>Food insufficiency Unemployment Food insufficiency In the most recent survey period that ended September 26, an estimated 13.6% of Monterey County adults, or approximately 37,300 adults, lived in households experiencing food insufficiency.
Using a model based upon data from the Food Security Supplement of the Current Population Survey, we estimate that in the most recent survey period, 11.2% of children, or approximately 12,300 children, experienced food insufficiency.
Because the Household Pulse Survey does not provide data at the county level, we use a model to estimate county-level food insufficiency.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Napa County</title>
      <link>/napa/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/napa/</guid>
      <description>Food insufficiency Unemployment Food insufficiency In the most recent survey period that ended September 26, an estimated 8.1% of Napa County adults, or approximately 7,580 adults, lived in households experiencing food insufficiency.
Using a model based upon data from the Food Security Supplement of the Current Population Survey, we estimate that in the most recent survey period, 7.2% of children, or approximately 1,970 children, experienced food insufficiency.
Because the Household Pulse Survey does not provide data at the county level, we use a model to estimate county-level food insufficiency.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nevada County</title>
      <link>/nevada/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/nevada/</guid>
      <description>Food insufficiency Unemployment Food insufficiency In the most recent survey period that ended September 26, an estimated 7.9% of Nevada County adults, or approximately 5,560 adults, lived in households experiencing food insufficiency.
Using a model based upon data from the Food Security Supplement of the Current Population Survey, we estimate that in the most recent survey period, 7.1% of children, or approximately 1,170 children, experienced food insufficiency.
Because the Household Pulse Survey does not provide data at the county level, we use a model to estimate county-level food insufficiency.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Orange County</title>
      <link>/orange/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/orange/</guid>
      <description>Food insufficiency Unemployment Food insufficiency In the most recent survey period that ended September 26, an estimated 8.6% of Orange County adults, or approximately 183,000 adults, lived in households experiencing food insufficiency.
Using a model based upon data from the Food Security Supplement of the Current Population Survey, we estimate that in the most recent survey period, 7.6% of children, or approximately 51,400 children, experienced food insufficiency.
Because the Household Pulse Survey does not provide data at the county level, we use a model to estimate county-level food insufficiency.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Placer County</title>
      <link>/placer/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/placer/</guid>
      <description>Food insufficiency Unemployment Food insufficiency In the most recent survey period that ended September 26, an estimated 7.6% of Placer County adults, or approximately 20,200 adults, lived in households experiencing food insufficiency.
Using a model based upon data from the Food Security Supplement of the Current Population Survey, we estimate that in the most recent survey period, 6.9% of children, or approximately 5,960 children, experienced food insufficiency.
Because the Household Pulse Survey does not provide data at the county level, we use a model to estimate county-level food insufficiency.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Plumas County</title>
      <link>/plumas/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/plumas/</guid>
      <description>Food insufficiency Unemployment Food insufficiency In the most recent survey period that ended September 26, an estimated 11.1% of Plumas County adults, or approximately 1,480 adults, lived in households experiencing food insufficiency.
Using a model based upon data from the Food Security Supplement of the Current Population Survey, we estimate that in the most recent survey period, 9.4% of children, or approximately 301 children, experienced food insufficiency.
Because the Household Pulse Survey does not provide data at the county level, we use a model to estimate county-level food insufficiency.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Riverside County</title>
      <link>/riverside/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/riverside/</guid>
      <description>Food insufficiency Unemployment Food insufficiency In the most recent survey period that ended September 26, an estimated 11.9% of Riverside County adults, or approximately 189,000 adults, lived in households experiencing food insufficiency.
Using a model based upon data from the Food Security Supplement of the Current Population Survey, we estimate that in the most recent survey period, 10.0% of children, or approximately 59,800 children, experienced food insufficiency.
Because the Household Pulse Survey does not provide data at the county level, we use a model to estimate county-level food insufficiency.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sacramento County</title>
      <link>/sacramento/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/sacramento/</guid>
      <description>Food insufficiency Unemployment Food insufficiency In the most recent survey period that ended September 26, an estimated 10.4% of Sacramento County adults, or approximately 106,000 adults, lived in households experiencing food insufficiency.
Using a model based upon data from the Food Security Supplement of the Current Population Survey, we estimate that in the most recent survey period, 8.9% of children, or approximately 31,600 children, experienced food insufficiency.
Because the Household Pulse Survey does not provide data at the county level, we use a model to estimate county-level food insufficiency.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>San Benito County</title>
      <link>/san-benito/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/san-benito/</guid>
      <description>Food insufficiency Unemployment Food insufficiency In the most recent survey period that ended September 26, an estimated 13.4% of San Benito County adults, or approximately 5,350 adults, lived in households experiencing food insufficiency.
Using a model based upon data from the Food Security Supplement of the Current Population Survey, we estimate that in the most recent survey period, 11.0% of children, or approximately 1,720 children, experienced food insufficiency.
Because the Household Pulse Survey does not provide data at the county level, we use a model to estimate county-level food insufficiency.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>San Bernardino County</title>
      <link>/san-bernardino/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/san-bernardino/</guid>
      <description>Food insufficiency Unemployment Food insufficiency In the most recent survey period that ended September 26, an estimated 11.7% of San Bernardino County adults, or approximately 161,000 adults, lived in households experiencing food insufficiency.
Using a model based upon data from the Food Security Supplement of the Current Population Survey, we estimate that in the most recent survey period, 9.8% of children, or approximately 54,600 children, experienced food insufficiency.
Because the Household Pulse Survey does not provide data at the county level, we use a model to estimate county-level food insufficiency.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>San Diego County</title>
      <link>/san-diego/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/san-diego/</guid>
      <description>Food insufficiency Unemployment Food insufficiency In the most recent survey period that ended September 26, an estimated 9.0% of San Diego County adults, or approximately 202,000 adults, lived in households experiencing food insufficiency.
Using a model based upon data from the Food Security Supplement of the Current Population Survey, we estimate that in the most recent survey period, 7.9% of children, or approximately 55,200 children, experienced food insufficiency.
Because the Household Pulse Survey does not provide data at the county level, we use a model to estimate county-level food insufficiency.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>San Francisco County</title>
      <link>/san-francisco/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/san-francisco/</guid>
      <description>Food insufficiency Unemployment Food insufficiency In the most recent survey period that ended September 26, an estimated 7.8% of San Francisco County adults, or approximately 51,000 adults, lived in households experiencing food insufficiency.
Using a model based upon data from the Food Security Supplement of the Current Population Survey, we estimate that in the most recent survey period, 7.1% of children, or approximately 8,170 children, experienced food insufficiency.
Because the Household Pulse Survey does not provide data at the county level, we use a model to estimate county-level food insufficiency.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>San Joaquin County</title>
      <link>/san-joaquin/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/san-joaquin/</guid>
      <description>Food insufficiency Unemployment Food insufficiency In the most recent survey period that ended September 26, an estimated 13.9% of San Joaquin County adults, or approximately 66,500 adults, lived in households experiencing food insufficiency.
Using a model based upon data from the Food Security Supplement of the Current Population Survey, we estimate that in the most recent survey period, 11.4% of children, or approximately 22,800 children, experienced food insufficiency.
Because the Household Pulse Survey does not provide data at the county level, we use a model to estimate county-level food insufficiency.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>San Luis Obispo County</title>
      <link>/san-luis-obispo/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/san-luis-obispo/</guid>
      <description>Food insufficiency Unemployment Food insufficiency In the most recent survey period that ended September 26, an estimated 7.1% of San Luis Obispo County adults, or approximately 14,200 adults, lived in households experiencing food insufficiency.
Using a model based upon data from the Food Security Supplement of the Current Population Survey, we estimate that in the most recent survey period, 6.6% of children, or approximately 3,180 children, experienced food insufficiency.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>San Mateo County</title>
      <link>/san-mateo/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/san-mateo/</guid>
      <description>Food insufficiency Unemployment Food insufficiency In the most recent survey period that ended September 26, an estimated 7.1% of San Mateo County adults, or approximately 37,100 adults, lived in households experiencing food insufficiency.
Using a model based upon data from the Food Security Supplement of the Current Population Survey, we estimate that in the most recent survey period, 6.6% of children, or approximately 9,960 children, experienced food insufficiency.
Because the Household Pulse Survey does not provide data at the county level, we use a model to estimate county-level food insufficiency.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Santa Barbara County</title>
      <link>/santa-barbara/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/santa-barbara/</guid>
      <description>Food insufficiency Unemployment Food insufficiency In the most recent survey period that ended September 26, an estimated 8.4% of Santa Barbara County adults, or approximately 24,900 adults, lived in households experiencing food insufficiency.
Using a model based upon data from the Food Security Supplement of the Current Population Survey, we estimate that in the most recent survey period, 7.5% of children, or approximately 7,190 children, experienced food insufficiency.
Because the Household Pulse Survey does not provide data at the county level, we use a model to estimate county-level food insufficiency.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Santa Clara County</title>
      <link>/santa-clara/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/santa-clara/</guid>
      <description>Food insufficiency Unemployment Food insufficiency In the most recent survey period that ended September 26, an estimated 7.2% of Santa Clara County adults, or approximately 93,100 adults, lived in households experiencing food insufficiency.
Using a model based upon data from the Food Security Supplement of the Current Population Survey, we estimate that in the most recent survey period, 6.6% of children, or approximately 27,000 children, experienced food insufficiency.
Because the Household Pulse Survey does not provide data at the county level, we use a model to estimate county-level food insufficiency.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Santa Cruz County</title>
      <link>/santa-cruz/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/santa-cruz/</guid>
      <description>Food insufficiency Unemployment Food insufficiency In the most recent survey period that ended September 26, an estimated 10.5% of Santa Cruz County adults, or approximately 19,900 adults, lived in households experiencing food insufficiency.
Using a model based upon data from the Food Security Supplement of the Current Population Survey, we estimate that in the most recent survey period, 9.0% of children, or approximately 4,550 children, experienced food insufficiency.
Because the Household Pulse Survey does not provide data at the county level, we use a model to estimate county-level food insufficiency.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shasta County</title>
      <link>/shasta/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/shasta/</guid>
      <description>Food insufficiency Unemployment Food insufficiency In the most recent survey period that ended September 26, an estimated 9.6% of Shasta County adults, or approximately 11,600 adults, lived in households experiencing food insufficiency.
Using a model based upon data from the Food Security Supplement of the Current Population Survey, we estimate that in the most recent survey period, 8.3% of children, or approximately 3,160 children, experienced food insufficiency.
Because the Household Pulse Survey does not provide data at the county level, we use a model to estimate county-level food insufficiency.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sierra County</title>
      <link>/sierra/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/sierra/</guid>
      <description>Food insufficiency Unemployment Food insufficiency In the most recent survey period that ended September 26, an estimated 7.6% of Sierra County adults, or approximately 163 adults, lived in households experiencing food insufficiency.
Using a model based upon data from the Food Security Supplement of the Current Population Survey, we estimate that in the most recent survey period, 6.9% of children, or approximately 34 children, experienced food insufficiency.
Because the Household Pulse Survey does not provide data at the county level, we use a model to estimate county-level food insufficiency.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Siskiyou County</title>
      <link>/siskiyou/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/siskiyou/</guid>
      <description>Food insufficiency Unemployment Food insufficiency In the most recent survey period that ended September 26, an estimated 10.1% of Siskiyou County adults, or approximately 3,000 adults, lived in households experiencing food insufficiency.
Using a model based upon data from the Food Security Supplement of the Current Population Survey, we estimate that in the most recent survey period, 8.7% of children, or approximately 741 children, experienced food insufficiency.
Because the Household Pulse Survey does not provide data at the county level, we use a model to estimate county-level food insufficiency.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Solano County</title>
      <link>/solano/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/solano/</guid>
      <description>Food insufficiency Unemployment Food insufficiency In the most recent survey period that ended September 26, an estimated 10.7% of Solano County adults, or approximately 32,100 adults, lived in households experiencing food insufficiency.
Using a model based upon data from the Food Security Supplement of the Current Population Survey, we estimate that in the most recent survey period, 9.1% of children, or approximately 8,800 children, experienced food insufficiency.
Because the Household Pulse Survey does not provide data at the county level, we use a model to estimate county-level food insufficiency.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sonoma County</title>
      <link>/sonoma/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/sonoma/</guid>
      <description>Food insufficiency Unemployment Food insufficiency In the most recent survey period that ended September 26, an estimated 7.8% of Sonoma County adults, or approximately 26,600 adults, lived in households experiencing food insufficiency.
Using a model based upon data from the Food Security Supplement of the Current Population Survey, we estimate that in the most recent survey period, 7.1% of children, or approximately 6,600 children, experienced food insufficiency.
Because the Household Pulse Survey does not provide data at the county level, we use a model to estimate county-level food insufficiency.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stanislaus County</title>
      <link>/stanislaus/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stanislaus/</guid>
      <description>Food insufficiency Unemployment Food insufficiency In the most recent survey period that ended September 26, an estimated 13.9% of Stanislaus County adults, or approximately 47,700 adults, lived in households experiencing food insufficiency.
Using a model based upon data from the Food Security Supplement of the Current Population Survey, we estimate that in the most recent survey period, 11.3% of children, or approximately 16,500 children, experienced food insufficiency.
Because the Household Pulse Survey does not provide data at the county level, we use a model to estimate county-level food insufficiency.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sutter County</title>
      <link>/sutter/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/sutter/</guid>
      <description>Food insufficiency Unemployment Food insufficiency In the most recent survey period that ended September 26, an estimated 16.1% of Sutter County adults, or approximately 9,900 adults, lived in households experiencing food insufficiency.
Using a model based upon data from the Food Security Supplement of the Current Population Survey, we estimate that in the most recent survey period, 12.9% of children, or approximately 3,150 children, experienced food insufficiency.
Because the Household Pulse Survey does not provide data at the county level, we use a model to estimate county-level food insufficiency.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tehama County</title>
      <link>/tehama/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/tehama/</guid>
      <description>Food insufficiency Unemployment Food insufficiency In the most recent survey period that ended September 26, an estimated 10.4% of Tehama County adults, or approximately 4,430 adults, lived in households experiencing food insufficiency.
Using a model based upon data from the Food Security Supplement of the Current Population Survey, we estimate that in the most recent survey period, 8.9% of children, or approximately 1,350 children, experienced food insufficiency.
Because the Household Pulse Survey does not provide data at the county level, we use a model to estimate county-level food insufficiency.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Trinity County</title>
      <link>/trinity/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/trinity/</guid>
      <description>Food insufficiency Unemployment Food insufficiency In the most recent survey period that ended September 26, an estimated 7.2% of Trinity County adults, or approximately 629 adults, lived in households experiencing food insufficiency.
Using a model based upon data from the Food Security Supplement of the Current Population Survey, we estimate that in the most recent survey period, 6.7% of children, or approximately 139 children, experienced food insufficiency.
Because the Household Pulse Survey does not provide data at the county level, we use a model to estimate county-level food insufficiency.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tulare County</title>
      <link>/tulare/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/tulare/</guid>
      <description>Food insufficiency Unemployment Food insufficiency In the most recent survey period that ended September 26, an estimated 22.4% of Tulare County adults, or approximately 62,000 adults, lived in households experiencing food insufficiency.
Using a model based upon data from the Food Security Supplement of the Current Population Survey, we estimate that in the most recent survey period, 17.4% of children, or approximately 24,100 children, experienced food insufficiency.
Because the Household Pulse Survey does not provide data at the county level, we use a model to estimate county-level food insufficiency.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tuolumne County</title>
      <link>/tuolumne/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/tuolumne/</guid>
      <description>Food insufficiency Unemployment Food insufficiency In the most recent survey period that ended September 26, an estimated 8.2% of Tuolumne County adults, or approximately 3,170 adults, lived in households experiencing food insufficiency.
Using a model based upon data from the Food Security Supplement of the Current Population Survey, we estimate that in the most recent survey period, 7.3% of children, or approximately 656 children, experienced food insufficiency.
Because the Household Pulse Survey does not provide data at the county level, we use a model to estimate county-level food insufficiency.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ventura County</title>
      <link>/ventura/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/ventura/</guid>
      <description>Food insufficiency Unemployment Food insufficiency In the most recent survey period that ended September 26, an estimated 9.7% of Ventura County adults, or approximately 54,200 adults, lived in households experiencing food insufficiency.
Using a model based upon data from the Food Security Supplement of the Current Population Survey, we estimate that in the most recent survey period, 8.4% of children, or approximately 15,700 children, experienced food insufficiency.
Because the Household Pulse Survey does not provide data at the county level, we use a model to estimate county-level food insufficiency.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Yolo County</title>
      <link>/yolo/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/yolo/</guid>
      <description>Food insufficiency Unemployment Food insufficiency In the most recent survey period that ended September 26, an estimated 9.5% of Yolo County adults, or approximately 14,200 adults, lived in households experiencing food insufficiency.
Using a model based upon data from the Food Security Supplement of the Current Population Survey, we estimate that in the most recent survey period, 8.2% of children, or approximately 3,690 children, experienced food insufficiency.
Because the Household Pulse Survey does not provide data at the county level, we use a model to estimate county-level food insufficiency.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Yuba County</title>
      <link>/yuba/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/yuba/</guid>
      <description>Food insufficiency Unemployment Food insufficiency In the most recent survey period that ended September 26, an estimated 12.7% of Yuba County adults, or approximately 6,210 adults, lived in households experiencing food insufficiency.
Using a model based upon data from the Food Security Supplement of the Current Population Survey, we estimate that in the most recent survey period, 10.5% of children, or approximately 2,230 children, experienced food insufficiency.
Because the Household Pulse Survey does not provide data at the county level, we use a model to estimate county-level food insufficiency.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
