<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>California Weekly Pulse</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on California Weekly Pulse</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 16 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description>The California Weekly Pulse site was created and is maintained by the Stanford Data Lab. If you have any feedback, comments, or suggestions for improvements to this site, please email us.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Alameda County</title>
      <link>/alameda/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/alameda/</guid>
      <description>Food insecurity Unemployment   Food insecurity The estimates of food insecurity in Alameda County are based upon a model. The model uses the overall rate of food insecurity for the state, which is updated every week, and the unemployment rate for each county, which is updated every month. The unemployment data for a month comes out later than the food insecurity data. For months where unemployment data is not yet available, the model uses the latest month for which data is available.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Alpine County</title>
      <link>/alpine/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/alpine/</guid>
      <description>Food insecurity Unemployment   Food insecurity The estimates of food insecurity in Alpine County are based upon a model. The model uses the overall rate of food insecurity for the state, which is updated every week, and the unemployment rate for each county, which is updated every month. The unemployment data for a month comes out later than the food insecurity data. For months where unemployment data is not yet available, the model uses the latest month for which data is available.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Amador County</title>
      <link>/amador/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/amador/</guid>
      <description>Food insecurity Unemployment   Food insecurity The estimates of food insecurity in Amador County are based upon a model. The model uses the overall rate of food insecurity for the state, which is updated every week, and the unemployment rate for each county, which is updated every month. The unemployment data for a month comes out later than the food insecurity data. For months where unemployment data is not yet available, the model uses the latest month for which data is available.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Butte County</title>
      <link>/butte/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/butte/</guid>
      <description>Food insecurity Unemployment   Food insecurity The estimates of food insecurity in Butte County are based upon a model. The model uses the overall rate of food insecurity for the state, which is updated every week, and the unemployment rate for each county, which is updated every month. The unemployment data for a month comes out later than the food insecurity data. For months where unemployment data is not yet available, the model uses the latest month for which data is available.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Calaveras County</title>
      <link>/calaveras/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/calaveras/</guid>
      <description>Food insecurity Unemployment   Food insecurity The estimates of food insecurity in Calaveras County are based upon a model. The model uses the overall rate of food insecurity for the state, which is updated every week, and the unemployment rate for each county, which is updated every month. The unemployment data for a month comes out later than the food insecurity data. For months where unemployment data is not yet available, the model uses the latest month for which data is available.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>California</title>
      <link>/state/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/state/</guid>
      <description>Overview Food insecurity Unemployment   Overview The data on this site is derived from the U.S. Census Bureau Household Pulse Survey (HPS) and the U.S. Bureau of Labor Statistics Local Area Unemployment Statistics (LAUS). New HPS data is released once a week, and new LAUS data is released once a month. The most recent data used for this report are:
 Household Pulse Survey: May 28 - June 2 Local Area Unemployment Statistics: April  The HPS releases data in two stages.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Colusa County</title>
      <link>/colusa/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/colusa/</guid>
      <description>Food insecurity Unemployment   Food insecurity The estimates of food insecurity in Colusa County are based upon a model. The model uses the overall rate of food insecurity for the state, which is updated every week, and the unemployment rate for each county, which is updated every month. The unemployment data for a month comes out later than the food insecurity data. For months where unemployment data is not yet available, the model uses the latest month for which data is available.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contra Costa County</title>
      <link>/contra-costa/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/contra-costa/</guid>
      <description>Food insecurity Unemployment   Food insecurity The estimates of food insecurity in Contra Costa County are based upon a model. The model uses the overall rate of food insecurity for the state, which is updated every week, and the unemployment rate for each county, which is updated every month. The unemployment data for a month comes out later than the food insecurity data. For months where unemployment data is not yet available, the model uses the latest month for which data is available.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Del Norte County</title>
      <link>/del-norte/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/del-norte/</guid>
      <description>Food insecurity Unemployment   Food insecurity The estimates of food insecurity in Del Norte County are based upon a model. The model uses the overall rate of food insecurity for the state, which is updated every week, and the unemployment rate for each county, which is updated every month. The unemployment data for a month comes out later than the food insecurity data. For months where unemployment data is not yet available, the model uses the latest month for which data is available.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>El Dorado County</title>
      <link>/el-dorado/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/el-dorado/</guid>
      <description>Food insecurity Unemployment   Food insecurity The estimates of food insecurity in El Dorado County are based upon a model. The model uses the overall rate of food insecurity for the state, which is updated every week, and the unemployment rate for each county, which is updated every month. The unemployment data for a month comes out later than the food insecurity data. For months where unemployment data is not yet available, the model uses the latest month for which data is available.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fresno County</title>
      <link>/fresno/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/fresno/</guid>
      <description>Food insecurity Unemployment   Food insecurity The estimates of food insecurity in Fresno County are based upon a model. The model uses the overall rate of food insecurity for the state, which is updated every week, and the unemployment rate for each county, which is updated every month. The unemployment data for a month comes out later than the food insecurity data. For months where unemployment data is not yet available, the model uses the latest month for which data is available.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Glenn County</title>
      <link>/glenn/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/glenn/</guid>
      <description>Food insecurity Unemployment   Food insecurity The estimates of food insecurity in Glenn County are based upon a model. The model uses the overall rate of food insecurity for the state, which is updated every week, and the unemployment rate for each county, which is updated every month. The unemployment data for a month comes out later than the food insecurity data. For months where unemployment data is not yet available, the model uses the latest month for which data is available.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Humboldt County</title>
      <link>/humboldt/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/humboldt/</guid>
      <description>Food insecurity Unemployment   Food insecurity The estimates of food insecurity in Humboldt County are based upon a model. The model uses the overall rate of food insecurity for the state, which is updated every week, and the unemployment rate for each county, which is updated every month. The unemployment data for a month comes out later than the food insecurity data. For months where unemployment data is not yet available, the model uses the latest month for which data is available.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Imperial County</title>
      <link>/imperial/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/imperial/</guid>
      <description>Food insecurity Unemployment   Food insecurity The estimates of food insecurity in Imperial County are based upon a model. The model uses the overall rate of food insecurity for the state, which is updated every week, and the unemployment rate for each county, which is updated every month. The unemployment data for a month comes out later than the food insecurity data. For months where unemployment data is not yet available, the model uses the latest month for which data is available.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Inyo County</title>
      <link>/inyo/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/inyo/</guid>
      <description>Food insecurity Unemployment   Food insecurity The estimates of food insecurity in Inyo County are based upon a model. The model uses the overall rate of food insecurity for the state, which is updated every week, and the unemployment rate for each county, which is updated every month. The unemployment data for a month comes out later than the food insecurity data. For months where unemployment data is not yet available, the model uses the latest month for which data is available.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kern County</title>
      <link>/kern/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/kern/</guid>
      <description>Food insecurity Unemployment   Food insecurity The estimates of food insecurity in Kern County are based upon a model. The model uses the overall rate of food insecurity for the state, which is updated every week, and the unemployment rate for each county, which is updated every month. The unemployment data for a month comes out later than the food insecurity data. For months where unemployment data is not yet available, the model uses the latest month for which data is available.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kings County</title>
      <link>/kings/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/kings/</guid>
      <description>Food insecurity Unemployment   Food insecurity The estimates of food insecurity in Kings County are based upon a model. The model uses the overall rate of food insecurity for the state, which is updated every week, and the unemployment rate for each county, which is updated every month. The unemployment data for a month comes out later than the food insecurity data. For months where unemployment data is not yet available, the model uses the latest month for which data is available.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lake County</title>
      <link>/lake/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/lake/</guid>
      <description>Food insecurity Unemployment   Food insecurity The estimates of food insecurity in Lake County are based upon a model. The model uses the overall rate of food insecurity for the state, which is updated every week, and the unemployment rate for each county, which is updated every month. The unemployment data for a month comes out later than the food insecurity data. For months where unemployment data is not yet available, the model uses the latest month for which data is available.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lassen County</title>
      <link>/lassen/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/lassen/</guid>
      <description>Food insecurity Unemployment   Food insecurity The estimates of food insecurity in Lassen County are based upon a model. The model uses the overall rate of food insecurity for the state, which is updated every week, and the unemployment rate for each county, which is updated every month. The unemployment data for a month comes out later than the food insecurity data. For months where unemployment data is not yet available, the model uses the latest month for which data is available.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Los Angeles County</title>
      <link>/los-angeles/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/los-angeles/</guid>
      <description>Food insecurity Unemployment   Food insecurity The estimates of food insecurity in Los Angeles County are based upon a model. The model uses the overall rate of food insecurity for the state, which is updated every week, and the unemployment rate for each county, which is updated every month. The unemployment data for a month comes out later than the food insecurity data. For months where unemployment data is not yet available, the model uses the latest month for which data is available.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Madera County</title>
      <link>/madera/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/madera/</guid>
      <description>Food insecurity Unemployment   Food insecurity The estimates of food insecurity in Madera County are based upon a model. The model uses the overall rate of food insecurity for the state, which is updated every week, and the unemployment rate for each county, which is updated every month. The unemployment data for a month comes out later than the food insecurity data. For months where unemployment data is not yet available, the model uses the latest month for which data is available.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Marin County</title>
      <link>/marin/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/marin/</guid>
      <description>Food insecurity Unemployment   Food insecurity The estimates of food insecurity in Marin County are based upon a model. The model uses the overall rate of food insecurity for the state, which is updated every week, and the unemployment rate for each county, which is updated every month. The unemployment data for a month comes out later than the food insecurity data. For months where unemployment data is not yet available, the model uses the latest month for which data is available.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mariposa County</title>
      <link>/mariposa/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/mariposa/</guid>
      <description>Food insecurity Unemployment   Food insecurity The estimates of food insecurity in Mariposa County are based upon a model. The model uses the overall rate of food insecurity for the state, which is updated every week, and the unemployment rate for each county, which is updated every month. The unemployment data for a month comes out later than the food insecurity data. For months where unemployment data is not yet available, the model uses the latest month for which data is available.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mendocino County</title>
      <link>/mendocino/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/mendocino/</guid>
      <description>Food insecurity Unemployment   Food insecurity The estimates of food insecurity in Mendocino County are based upon a model. The model uses the overall rate of food insecurity for the state, which is updated every week, and the unemployment rate for each county, which is updated every month. The unemployment data for a month comes out later than the food insecurity data. For months where unemployment data is not yet available, the model uses the latest month for which data is available.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Merced County</title>
      <link>/merced/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/merced/</guid>
      <description>Food insecurity Unemployment   Food insecurity The estimates of food insecurity in Merced County are based upon a model. The model uses the overall rate of food insecurity for the state, which is updated every week, and the unemployment rate for each county, which is updated every month. The unemployment data for a month comes out later than the food insecurity data. For months where unemployment data is not yet available, the model uses the latest month for which data is available.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Modoc County</title>
      <link>/modoc/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/modoc/</guid>
      <description>Food insecurity Unemployment   Food insecurity The estimates of food insecurity in Modoc County are based upon a model. The model uses the overall rate of food insecurity for the state, which is updated every week, and the unemployment rate for each county, which is updated every month. The unemployment data for a month comes out later than the food insecurity data. For months where unemployment data is not yet available, the model uses the latest month for which data is available.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mono County</title>
      <link>/mono/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/mono/</guid>
      <description>Food insecurity Unemployment   Food insecurity The estimates of food insecurity in Mono County are based upon a model. The model uses the overall rate of food insecurity for the state, which is updated every week, and the unemployment rate for each county, which is updated every month. The unemployment data for a month comes out later than the food insecurity data. For months where unemployment data is not yet available, the model uses the latest month for which data is available.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Monterey County</title>
      <link>/monterey/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/monterey/</guid>
      <description>Food insecurity Unemployment   Food insecurity The estimates of food insecurity in Monterey County are based upon a model. The model uses the overall rate of food insecurity for the state, which is updated every week, and the unemployment rate for each county, which is updated every month. The unemployment data for a month comes out later than the food insecurity data. For months where unemployment data is not yet available, the model uses the latest month for which data is available.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Napa County</title>
      <link>/napa/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/napa/</guid>
      <description>Food insecurity Unemployment   Food insecurity The estimates of food insecurity in Napa County are based upon a model. The model uses the overall rate of food insecurity for the state, which is updated every week, and the unemployment rate for each county, which is updated every month. The unemployment data for a month comes out later than the food insecurity data. For months where unemployment data is not yet available, the model uses the latest month for which data is available.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nevada County</title>
      <link>/nevada/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/nevada/</guid>
      <description>Food insecurity Unemployment   Food insecurity The estimates of food insecurity in Nevada County are based upon a model. The model uses the overall rate of food insecurity for the state, which is updated every week, and the unemployment rate for each county, which is updated every month. The unemployment data for a month comes out later than the food insecurity data. For months where unemployment data is not yet available, the model uses the latest month for which data is available.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Orange County</title>
      <link>/orange/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/orange/</guid>
      <description>Food insecurity Unemployment   Food insecurity The estimates of food insecurity in Orange County are based upon a model. The model uses the overall rate of food insecurity for the state, which is updated every week, and the unemployment rate for each county, which is updated every month. The unemployment data for a month comes out later than the food insecurity data. For months where unemployment data is not yet available, the model uses the latest month for which data is available.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Placer County</title>
      <link>/placer/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/placer/</guid>
      <description>Food insecurity Unemployment   Food insecurity The estimates of food insecurity in Placer County are based upon a model. The model uses the overall rate of food insecurity for the state, which is updated every week, and the unemployment rate for each county, which is updated every month. The unemployment data for a month comes out later than the food insecurity data. For months where unemployment data is not yet available, the model uses the latest month for which data is available.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Plumas County</title>
      <link>/plumas/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/plumas/</guid>
      <description>Food insecurity Unemployment   Food insecurity The estimates of food insecurity in Plumas County are based upon a model. The model uses the overall rate of food insecurity for the state, which is updated every week, and the unemployment rate for each county, which is updated every month. The unemployment data for a month comes out later than the food insecurity data. For months where unemployment data is not yet available, the model uses the latest month for which data is available.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Riverside County</title>
      <link>/riverside/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/riverside/</guid>
      <description>Food insecurity Unemployment   Food insecurity The estimates of food insecurity in Riverside County are based upon a model. The model uses the overall rate of food insecurity for the state, which is updated every week, and the unemployment rate for each county, which is updated every month. The unemployment data for a month comes out later than the food insecurity data. For months where unemployment data is not yet available, the model uses the latest month for which data is available.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sacramento County</title>
      <link>/sacramento/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/sacramento/</guid>
      <description>Food insecurity Unemployment   Food insecurity The estimates of food insecurity in Sacramento County are based upon a model. The model uses the overall rate of food insecurity for the state, which is updated every week, and the unemployment rate for each county, which is updated every month. The unemployment data for a month comes out later than the food insecurity data. For months where unemployment data is not yet available, the model uses the latest month for which data is available.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>San Benito County</title>
      <link>/san-benito/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/san-benito/</guid>
      <description>Food insecurity Unemployment   Food insecurity The estimates of food insecurity in San Benito County are based upon a model. The model uses the overall rate of food insecurity for the state, which is updated every week, and the unemployment rate for each county, which is updated every month. The unemployment data for a month comes out later than the food insecurity data. For months where unemployment data is not yet available, the model uses the latest month for which data is available.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>San Bernardino County</title>
      <link>/san-bernardino/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/san-bernardino/</guid>
      <description>Food insecurity Unemployment   Food insecurity The estimates of food insecurity in San Bernardino County are based upon a model. The model uses the overall rate of food insecurity for the state, which is updated every week, and the unemployment rate for each county, which is updated every month. The unemployment data for a month comes out later than the food insecurity data. For months where unemployment data is not yet available, the model uses the latest month for which data is available.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>San Diego County</title>
      <link>/san-diego/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/san-diego/</guid>
      <description>Food insecurity Unemployment   Food insecurity The estimates of food insecurity in San Diego County are based upon a model. The model uses the overall rate of food insecurity for the state, which is updated every week, and the unemployment rate for each county, which is updated every month. The unemployment data for a month comes out later than the food insecurity data. For months where unemployment data is not yet available, the model uses the latest month for which data is available.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>San Francisco County</title>
      <link>/san-francisco/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/san-francisco/</guid>
      <description>Food insecurity Unemployment   Food insecurity The estimates of food insecurity in San Francisco County are based upon a model. The model uses the overall rate of food insecurity for the state, which is updated every week, and the unemployment rate for each county, which is updated every month. The unemployment data for a month comes out later than the food insecurity data. For months where unemployment data is not yet available, the model uses the latest month for which data is available.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>San Joaquin County</title>
      <link>/san-joaquin/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/san-joaquin/</guid>
      <description>Food insecurity Unemployment   Food insecurity The estimates of food insecurity in San Joaquin County are based upon a model. The model uses the overall rate of food insecurity for the state, which is updated every week, and the unemployment rate for each county, which is updated every month. The unemployment data for a month comes out later than the food insecurity data. For months where unemployment data is not yet available, the model uses the latest month for which data is available.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>San Luis Obispo County</title>
      <link>/san-luis-obispo/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/san-luis-obispo/</guid>
      <description>Food insecurity Unemployment   Food insecurity The estimates of food insecurity in San Luis Obispo County are based upon a model. The model uses the overall rate of food insecurity for the state, which is updated every week, and the unemployment rate for each county, which is updated every month. The unemployment data for a month comes out later than the food insecurity data. For months where unemployment data is not yet available, the model uses the latest month for which data is available.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>San Mateo County</title>
      <link>/san-mateo/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/san-mateo/</guid>
      <description>Food insecurity Unemployment   Food insecurity The estimates of food insecurity in San Mateo County are based upon a model. The model uses the overall rate of food insecurity for the state, which is updated every week, and the unemployment rate for each county, which is updated every month. The unemployment data for a month comes out later than the food insecurity data. For months where unemployment data is not yet available, the model uses the latest month for which data is available.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Santa Barbara County</title>
      <link>/santa-barbara/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/santa-barbara/</guid>
      <description>Food insecurity Unemployment   Food insecurity The estimates of food insecurity in Santa Barbara County are based upon a model. The model uses the overall rate of food insecurity for the state, which is updated every week, and the unemployment rate for each county, which is updated every month. The unemployment data for a month comes out later than the food insecurity data. For months where unemployment data is not yet available, the model uses the latest month for which data is available.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Santa Clara County</title>
      <link>/santa-clara/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/santa-clara/</guid>
      <description>Food insecurity Unemployment   Food insecurity The estimates of food insecurity in Santa Clara County are based upon a model. The model uses the overall rate of food insecurity for the state, which is updated every week, and the unemployment rate for each county, which is updated every month. The unemployment data for a month comes out later than the food insecurity data. For months where unemployment data is not yet available, the model uses the latest month for which data is available.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Santa Cruz County</title>
      <link>/santa-cruz/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/santa-cruz/</guid>
      <description>Food insecurity Unemployment   Food insecurity The estimates of food insecurity in Santa Cruz County are based upon a model. The model uses the overall rate of food insecurity for the state, which is updated every week, and the unemployment rate for each county, which is updated every month. The unemployment data for a month comes out later than the food insecurity data. For months where unemployment data is not yet available, the model uses the latest month for which data is available.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shasta County</title>
      <link>/shasta/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/shasta/</guid>
      <description>Food insecurity Unemployment   Food insecurity The estimates of food insecurity in Shasta County are based upon a model. The model uses the overall rate of food insecurity for the state, which is updated every week, and the unemployment rate for each county, which is updated every month. The unemployment data for a month comes out later than the food insecurity data. For months where unemployment data is not yet available, the model uses the latest month for which data is available.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sierra County</title>
      <link>/sierra/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/sierra/</guid>
      <description>Food insecurity Unemployment   Food insecurity The estimates of food insecurity in Sierra County are based upon a model. The model uses the overall rate of food insecurity for the state, which is updated every week, and the unemployment rate for each county, which is updated every month. The unemployment data for a month comes out later than the food insecurity data. For months where unemployment data is not yet available, the model uses the latest month for which data is available.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Siskiyou County</title>
      <link>/siskiyou/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/siskiyou/</guid>
      <description>Food insecurity Unemployment   Food insecurity The estimates of food insecurity in Siskiyou County are based upon a model. The model uses the overall rate of food insecurity for the state, which is updated every week, and the unemployment rate for each county, which is updated every month. The unemployment data for a month comes out later than the food insecurity data. For months where unemployment data is not yet available, the model uses the latest month for which data is available.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Solano County</title>
      <link>/solano/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/solano/</guid>
      <description>Food insecurity Unemployment   Food insecurity The estimates of food insecurity in Solano County are based upon a model. The model uses the overall rate of food insecurity for the state, which is updated every week, and the unemployment rate for each county, which is updated every month. The unemployment data for a month comes out later than the food insecurity data. For months where unemployment data is not yet available, the model uses the latest month for which data is available.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sonoma County</title>
      <link>/sonoma/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/sonoma/</guid>
      <description>Food insecurity Unemployment   Food insecurity The estimates of food insecurity in Sonoma County are based upon a model. The model uses the overall rate of food insecurity for the state, which is updated every week, and the unemployment rate for each county, which is updated every month. The unemployment data for a month comes out later than the food insecurity data. For months where unemployment data is not yet available, the model uses the latest month for which data is available.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stanislaus County</title>
      <link>/stanislaus/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stanislaus/</guid>
      <description>Food insecurity Unemployment   Food insecurity The estimates of food insecurity in Stanislaus County are based upon a model. The model uses the overall rate of food insecurity for the state, which is updated every week, and the unemployment rate for each county, which is updated every month. The unemployment data for a month comes out later than the food insecurity data. For months where unemployment data is not yet available, the model uses the latest month for which data is available.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sutter County</title>
      <link>/sutter/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/sutter/</guid>
      <description>Food insecurity Unemployment   Food insecurity The estimates of food insecurity in Sutter County are based upon a model. The model uses the overall rate of food insecurity for the state, which is updated every week, and the unemployment rate for each county, which is updated every month. The unemployment data for a month comes out later than the food insecurity data. For months where unemployment data is not yet available, the model uses the latest month for which data is available.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tehama County</title>
      <link>/tehama/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/tehama/</guid>
      <description>Food insecurity Unemployment   Food insecurity The estimates of food insecurity in Tehama County are based upon a model. The model uses the overall rate of food insecurity for the state, which is updated every week, and the unemployment rate for each county, which is updated every month. The unemployment data for a month comes out later than the food insecurity data. For months where unemployment data is not yet available, the model uses the latest month for which data is available.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Trinity County</title>
      <link>/trinity/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/trinity/</guid>
      <description>Food insecurity Unemployment   Food insecurity The estimates of food insecurity in Trinity County are based upon a model. The model uses the overall rate of food insecurity for the state, which is updated every week, and the unemployment rate for each county, which is updated every month. The unemployment data for a month comes out later than the food insecurity data. For months where unemployment data is not yet available, the model uses the latest month for which data is available.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tulare County</title>
      <link>/tulare/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/tulare/</guid>
      <description>Food insecurity Unemployment   Food insecurity The estimates of food insecurity in Tulare County are based upon a model. The model uses the overall rate of food insecurity for the state, which is updated every week, and the unemployment rate for each county, which is updated every month. The unemployment data for a month comes out later than the food insecurity data. For months where unemployment data is not yet available, the model uses the latest month for which data is available.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tuolumne County</title>
      <link>/tuolumne/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/tuolumne/</guid>
      <description>Food insecurity Unemployment   Food insecurity The estimates of food insecurity in Tuolumne County are based upon a model. The model uses the overall rate of food insecurity for the state, which is updated every week, and the unemployment rate for each county, which is updated every month. The unemployment data for a month comes out later than the food insecurity data. For months where unemployment data is not yet available, the model uses the latest month for which data is available.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ventura County</title>
      <link>/ventura/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/ventura/</guid>
      <description>Food insecurity Unemployment   Food insecurity The estimates of food insecurity in Ventura County are based upon a model. The model uses the overall rate of food insecurity for the state, which is updated every week, and the unemployment rate for each county, which is updated every month. The unemployment data for a month comes out later than the food insecurity data. For months where unemployment data is not yet available, the model uses the latest month for which data is available.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Yolo County</title>
      <link>/yolo/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/yolo/</guid>
      <description>Food insecurity Unemployment   Food insecurity The estimates of food insecurity in Yolo County are based upon a model. The model uses the overall rate of food insecurity for the state, which is updated every week, and the unemployment rate for each county, which is updated every month. The unemployment data for a month comes out later than the food insecurity data. For months where unemployment data is not yet available, the model uses the latest month for which data is available.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Yuba County</title>
      <link>/yuba/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/yuba/</guid>
      <description>Food insecurity Unemployment   Food insecurity The estimates of food insecurity in Yuba County are based upon a model. The model uses the overall rate of food insecurity for the state, which is updated every week, and the unemployment rate for each county, which is updated every month. The unemployment data for a month comes out later than the food insecurity data. For months where unemployment data is not yet available, the model uses the latest month for which data is available.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>