<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>California Pulse</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on California Pulse</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description>The California Weekly Pulse site was created and is maintained by the Stanford Data Lab. If you have any feedback, comments, or suggestions for improvements to this site, please email us.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Alameda County</title>
      <link>/alameda/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/alameda/</guid>
      <description>Food insufficiency Unemployment Food insufficiency In the most recent survey period that ended December 19, an estimated 7.9% of Alameda County adults, or approximately 92,400 adults, lived in households experiencing food insufficiency.
Using a model based upon data from the Food Security Supplement of the Current Population Survey, we estimate that in the most recent survey period, 7.1% of children, or approximately 23,600 children, experienced food insufficiency.
Because the Household Pulse Survey does not provide data at the county level, we use a model to estimate county-level food insufficiency.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Alpine County</title>
      <link>/alpine/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/alpine/</guid>
      <description>Food insufficiency Unemployment Food insufficiency In the most recent survey period that ended December 19, an estimated 11.4% of Alpine County adults, or approximately 93 adults, lived in households experiencing food insufficiency.
Using a model based upon data from the Food Security Supplement of the Current Population Survey, we estimate that in the most recent survey period, 9.6% of children, or approximately 19 children, experienced food insufficiency.
Because the Household Pulse Survey does not provide data at the county level, we use a model to estimate county-level food insufficiency.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Amador County</title>
      <link>/amador/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/amador/</guid>
      <description>Food insufficiency Unemployment Food insufficiency In the most recent survey period that ended December 19, an estimated 7.7% of Amador County adults, or approximately 2,280 adults, lived in households experiencing food insufficiency.
Using a model based upon data from the Food Security Supplement of the Current Population Survey, we estimate that in the most recent survey period, 7.0% of children, or approximately 409 children, experienced food insufficiency.
Because the Household Pulse Survey does not provide data at the county level, we use a model to estimate county-level food insufficiency.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Butte County</title>
      <link>/butte/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/butte/</guid>
      <description>Food insufficiency Unemployment Food insufficiency In the most recent survey period that ended December 19, an estimated 9.3% of Butte County adults, or approximately 14,400 adults, lived in households experiencing food insufficiency.
Using a model based upon data from the Food Security Supplement of the Current Population Survey, we estimate that in the most recent survey period, 8.1% of children, or approximately 3,530 children, experienced food insufficiency.
Because the Household Pulse Survey does not provide data at the county level, we use a model to estimate county-level food insufficiency.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Calaveras County</title>
      <link>/calaveras/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/calaveras/</guid>
      <description>Food insufficiency Unemployment Food insufficiency In the most recent survey period that ended December 19, an estimated 8.0% of Calaveras County adults, or approximately 2,680 adults, lived in households experiencing food insufficiency.
Using a model based upon data from the Food Security Supplement of the Current Population Survey, we estimate that in the most recent survey period, 7.2% of children, or approximately 550 children, experienced food insufficiency.
Because the Household Pulse Survey does not provide data at the county level, we use a model to estimate county-level food insufficiency.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>California</title>
      <link>/state/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/state/</guid>
      <description>Overview Food insufficiency Rate over time Geography Demographics Reasons Severity Supplemental Nutrition Assitance Program (SNAP) Free groceries Unemployment Rate over time Geography Unemployment and food insufficiency Overview The data on this site is derived from the U.S. Census Bureau Household Pulse Survey (HPS) and the U.S. Bureau of Labor Statistics Local Area Unemployment Statistics (LAUS). New HPS data is currently released every four weeks, and new LAUS data is released once a month.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Colusa County</title>
      <link>/colusa/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/colusa/</guid>
      <description>Food insufficiency Unemployment Food insufficiency In the most recent survey period that ended December 19, an estimated 28.9% of Colusa County adults, or approximately 4,010 adults, lived in households experiencing food insufficiency.
Using a model based upon data from the Food Security Supplement of the Current Population Survey, we estimate that in the most recent survey period, 22.0% of children, or approximately 1,260 children, experienced food insufficiency.
Because the Household Pulse Survey does not provide data at the county level, we use a model to estimate county-level food insufficiency.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contra Costa County</title>
      <link>/contra-costa/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/contra-costa/</guid>
      <description>Food insufficiency Unemployment Food insufficiency In the most recent survey period that ended December 19, an estimated 8.4% of Contra Costa County adults, or approximately 66,600 adults, lived in households experiencing food insufficiency.
Using a model based upon data from the Food Security Supplement of the Current Population Survey, we estimate that in the most recent survey period, 7.5% of children, or approximately 19,000 children, experienced food insufficiency.
Because the Household Pulse Survey does not provide data at the county level, we use a model to estimate county-level food insufficiency.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Del Norte County</title>
      <link>/del-norte/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/del-norte/</guid>
      <description>Food insufficiency Unemployment Food insufficiency In the most recent survey period that ended December 19, an estimated 8.6% of Del Norte County adults, or approximately 1,680 adults, lived in households experiencing food insufficiency.
Using a model based upon data from the Food Security Supplement of the Current Population Survey, we estimate that in the most recent survey period, 7.7% of children, or approximately 436 children, experienced food insufficiency.
Because the Household Pulse Survey does not provide data at the county level, we use a model to estimate county-level food insufficiency.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>El Dorado County</title>
      <link>/el-dorado/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/el-dorado/</guid>
      <description>Food insufficiency Unemployment Food insufficiency In the most recent survey period that ended December 19, an estimated 7.6% of El Dorado County adults, or approximately 10,400 adults, lived in households experiencing food insufficiency.
Using a model based upon data from the Food Security Supplement of the Current Population Survey, we estimate that in the most recent survey period, 7.0% of children, or approximately 2,590 children, experienced food insufficiency.
Because the Household Pulse Survey does not provide data at the county level, we use a model to estimate county-level food insufficiency.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fresno County</title>
      <link>/fresno/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/fresno/</guid>
      <description>Food insufficiency Unemployment Food insufficiency In the most recent survey period that ended December 19, an estimated 16.7% of Fresno County adults, or approximately 105,000 adults, lived in households experiencing food insufficiency.
Using a model based upon data from the Food Security Supplement of the Current Population Survey, we estimate that in the most recent survey period, 13.3% of children, or approximately 36,700 children, experienced food insufficiency.
Because the Household Pulse Survey does not provide data at the county level, we use a model to estimate county-level food insufficiency.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Glenn County</title>
      <link>/glenn/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/glenn/</guid>
      <description>Food insufficiency Unemployment Food insufficiency In the most recent survey period that ended December 19, an estimated 12.6% of Glenn County adults, or approximately 2,320 adults, lived in households experiencing food insufficiency.
Using a model based upon data from the Food Security Supplement of the Current Population Survey, we estimate that in the most recent survey period, 10.5% of children, or approximately 774 children, experienced food insufficiency.
Because the Household Pulse Survey does not provide data at the county level, we use a model to estimate county-level food insufficiency.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Humboldt County</title>
      <link>/humboldt/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/humboldt/</guid>
      <description>Food insufficiency Unemployment Food insufficiency In the most recent survey period that ended December 19, an estimated 8.2% of Humboldt County adults, or approximately 7,980 adults, lived in households experiencing food insufficiency.
Using a model based upon data from the Food Security Supplement of the Current Population Survey, we estimate that in the most recent survey period, 7.4% of children, or approximately 1,850 children, experienced food insufficiency.
Because the Household Pulse Survey does not provide data at the county level, we use a model to estimate county-level food insufficiency.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Imperial County</title>
      <link>/imperial/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/imperial/</guid>
      <description>Food insufficiency Unemployment Food insufficiency In the most recent survey period that ended December 19, an estimated 36.7% of Imperial County adults, or approximately 42,000 adults, lived in households experiencing food insufficiency.
Using a model based upon data from the Food Security Supplement of the Current Population Survey, we estimate that in the most recent survey period, 27.5% of children, or approximately 13,900 children, experienced food insufficiency.
Because the Household Pulse Survey does not provide data at the county level, we use a model to estimate county-level food insufficiency.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Inyo County</title>
      <link>/inyo/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/inyo/</guid>
      <description>Food insufficiency Unemployment Food insufficiency In the most recent survey period that ended December 19, an estimated 7.7% of Inyo County adults, or approximately 978 adults, lived in households experiencing food insufficiency.
Using a model based upon data from the Food Security Supplement of the Current Population Survey, we estimate that in the most recent survey period, 7.0% of children, or approximately 256 children, experienced food insufficiency.
Because the Household Pulse Survey does not provide data at the county level, we use a model to estimate county-level food insufficiency.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kern County</title>
      <link>/kern/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/kern/</guid>
      <description>Food insufficiency Unemployment Food insufficiency In the most recent survey period that ended December 19, an estimated 16.6% of Kern County adults, or approximately 94,100 adults, lived in households experiencing food insufficiency.
Using a model based upon data from the Food Security Supplement of the Current Population Survey, we estimate that in the most recent survey period, 13.3% of children, or approximately 33,700 children, experienced food insufficiency.
Because the Household Pulse Survey does not provide data at the county level, we use a model to estimate county-level food insufficiency.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kings County</title>
      <link>/kings/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/kings/</guid>
      <description>Food insufficiency Unemployment Food insufficiency In the most recent survey period that ended December 19, an estimated 14.1% of Kings County adults, or approximately 13,900 adults, lived in households experiencing food insufficiency.
Using a model based upon data from the Food Security Supplement of the Current Population Survey, we estimate that in the most recent survey period, 11.5% of children, or approximately 4,650 children, experienced food insufficiency.
Because the Household Pulse Survey does not provide data at the county level, we use a model to estimate county-level food insufficiency.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lake County</title>
      <link>/lake/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/lake/</guid>
      <description>Food insufficiency Unemployment Food insufficiency In the most recent survey period that ended December 19, an estimated 11.8% of Lake County adults, or approximately 5,260 adults, lived in households experiencing food insufficiency.
Using a model based upon data from the Food Security Supplement of the Current Population Survey, we estimate that in the most recent survey period, 9.9% of children, or approximately 1,310 children, experienced food insufficiency.
Because the Household Pulse Survey does not provide data at the county level, we use a model to estimate county-level food insufficiency.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lassen County</title>
      <link>/lassen/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/lassen/</guid>
      <description>Food insufficiency Unemployment Food insufficiency In the most recent survey period that ended December 19, an estimated 5.8% of Lassen County adults, or approximately 1,300 adults, lived in households experiencing food insufficiency.
Using a model based upon data from the Food Security Supplement of the Current Population Survey, we estimate that in the most recent survey period, 5.7% of children, or approximately 293 children, experienced food insufficiency.
Because the Household Pulse Survey does not provide data at the county level, we use a model to estimate county-level food insufficiency.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Los Angeles County</title>
      <link>/los-angeles/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/los-angeles/</guid>
      <description>Food insufficiency Unemployment Food insufficiency In the most recent survey period that ended December 19, an estimated 11.3% of Los Angeles County adults, or approximately 788,000 adults, lived in households experiencing food insufficiency.
Using a model based upon data from the Food Security Supplement of the Current Population Survey, we estimate that in the most recent survey period, 9.5% of children, or approximately 2e+05 children, experienced food insufficiency.
Because the Household Pulse Survey does not provide data at the county level, we use a model to estimate county-level food insufficiency.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Madera County</title>
      <link>/madera/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/madera/</guid>
      <description>Food insufficiency Unemployment Food insufficiency In the most recent survey period that ended December 19, an estimated 13.7% of Madera County adults, or approximately 13,800 adults, lived in households experiencing food insufficiency.
Using a model based upon data from the Food Security Supplement of the Current Population Survey, we estimate that in the most recent survey period, 11.2% of children, or approximately 4,740 children, experienced food insufficiency.
Because the Household Pulse Survey does not provide data at the county level, we use a model to estimate county-level food insufficiency.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Marin County</title>
      <link>/marin/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/marin/</guid>
      <description>Food insufficiency Unemployment Food insufficiency In the most recent survey period that ended December 19, an estimated 6.1% of Marin County adults, or approximately 11,200 adults, lived in households experiencing food insufficiency.
Using a model based upon data from the Food Security Supplement of the Current Population Survey, we estimate that in the most recent survey period, 5.9% of children, or approximately 2,950 children, experienced food insufficiency.
Because the Household Pulse Survey does not provide data at the county level, we use a model to estimate county-level food insufficiency.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mariposa County</title>
      <link>/mariposa/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/mariposa/</guid>
      <description>Food insufficiency Unemployment Food insufficiency In the most recent survey period that ended December 19, an estimated 8.7% of Mariposa County adults, or approximately 1,110 adults, lived in households experiencing food insufficiency.
Using a model based upon data from the Food Security Supplement of the Current Population Survey, we estimate that in the most recent survey period, 7.7% of children, or approximately 210 children, experienced food insufficiency.
Because the Household Pulse Survey does not provide data at the county level, we use a model to estimate county-level food insufficiency.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mendocino County</title>
      <link>/mendocino/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/mendocino/</guid>
      <description>Food insufficiency Unemployment Food insufficiency In the most recent survey period that ended December 19, an estimated 8.6% of Mendocino County adults, or approximately 5,210 adults, lived in households experiencing food insufficiency.
Using a model based upon data from the Food Security Supplement of the Current Population Survey, we estimate that in the most recent survey period, 7.7% of children, or approximately 1,370 children, experienced food insufficiency.
Because the Household Pulse Survey does not provide data at the county level, we use a model to estimate county-level food insufficiency.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Merced County</title>
      <link>/merced/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/merced/</guid>
      <description>Food insufficiency Unemployment Food insufficiency In the most recent survey period that ended December 19, an estimated 17.2% of Merced County adults, or approximately 29,800 adults, lived in households experiencing food insufficiency.
Using a model based upon data from the Food Security Supplement of the Current Population Survey, we estimate that in the most recent survey period, 13.7% of children, or approximately 10,900 children, experienced food insufficiency.
Because the Household Pulse Survey does not provide data at the county level, we use a model to estimate county-level food insufficiency.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Modoc County</title>
      <link>/modoc/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/modoc/</guid>
      <description>Food insufficiency Unemployment Food insufficiency In the most recent survey period that ended December 19, an estimated 8.4% of Modoc County adults, or approximately 526 adults, lived in households experiencing food insufficiency.
Using a model based upon data from the Food Security Supplement of the Current Population Survey, we estimate that in the most recent survey period, 7.5% of children, or approximately 126 children, experienced food insufficiency.
Because the Household Pulse Survey does not provide data at the county level, we use a model to estimate county-level food insufficiency.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mono County</title>
      <link>/mono/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/mono/</guid>
      <description>Food insufficiency Unemployment Food insufficiency In the most recent survey period that ended December 19, an estimated 10.8% of Mono County adults, or approximately 1,130 adults, lived in households experiencing food insufficiency.
Using a model based upon data from the Food Security Supplement of the Current Population Survey, we estimate that in the most recent survey period, 9.2% of children, or approximately 230 children, experienced food insufficiency.
Because the Household Pulse Survey does not provide data at the county level, we use a model to estimate county-level food insufficiency.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Monterey County</title>
      <link>/monterey/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/monterey/</guid>
      <description>Food insufficiency Unemployment Food insufficiency In the most recent survey period that ended December 19, an estimated 14.4% of Monterey County adults, or approximately 40,900 adults, lived in households experiencing food insufficiency.
Using a model based upon data from the Food Security Supplement of the Current Population Survey, we estimate that in the most recent survey period, 11.8% of children, or approximately 13,000 children, experienced food insufficiency.
Because the Household Pulse Survey does not provide data at the county level, we use a model to estimate county-level food insufficiency.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Napa County</title>
      <link>/napa/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/napa/</guid>
      <description>Food insufficiency Unemployment Food insufficiency In the most recent survey period that ended December 19, an estimated 7.9% of Napa County adults, or approximately 7,610 adults, lived in households experiencing food insufficiency.
Using a model based upon data from the Food Security Supplement of the Current Population Survey, we estimate that in the most recent survey period, 7.1% of children, or approximately 1,930 children, experienced food insufficiency.
Because the Household Pulse Survey does not provide data at the county level, we use a model to estimate county-level food insufficiency.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nevada County</title>
      <link>/nevada/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/nevada/</guid>
      <description>Food insufficiency Unemployment Food insufficiency In the most recent survey period that ended December 19, an estimated 7.4% of Nevada County adults, or approximately 5,380 adults, lived in households experiencing food insufficiency.
Using a model based upon data from the Food Security Supplement of the Current Population Survey, we estimate that in the most recent survey period, 6.7% of children, or approximately 1,120 children, experienced food insufficiency.
Because the Household Pulse Survey does not provide data at the county level, we use a model to estimate county-level food insufficiency.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Orange County</title>
      <link>/orange/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/orange/</guid>
      <description>Food insufficiency Unemployment Food insufficiency In the most recent survey period that ended December 19, an estimated 7.7% of Orange County adults, or approximately 168,000 adults, lived in households experiencing food insufficiency.
Using a model based upon data from the Food Security Supplement of the Current Population Survey, we estimate that in the most recent survey period, 7.0% of children, or approximately 47,000 children, experienced food insufficiency.
Because the Household Pulse Survey does not provide data at the county level, we use a model to estimate county-level food insufficiency.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Placer County</title>
      <link>/placer/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/placer/</guid>
      <description>Food insufficiency Unemployment Food insufficiency In the most recent survey period that ended December 19, an estimated 7.1% of Placer County adults, or approximately 19,300 adults, lived in households experiencing food insufficiency.
Using a model based upon data from the Food Security Supplement of the Current Population Survey, we estimate that in the most recent survey period, 6.5% of children, or approximately 5,630 children, experienced food insufficiency.
Because the Household Pulse Survey does not provide data at the county level, we use a model to estimate county-level food insufficiency.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Plumas County</title>
      <link>/plumas/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/plumas/</guid>
      <description>Food insufficiency Unemployment Food insufficiency In the most recent survey period that ended December 19, an estimated 11.7% of Plumas County adults, or approximately 1,610 adults, lived in households experiencing food insufficiency.
Using a model based upon data from the Food Security Supplement of the Current Population Survey, we estimate that in the most recent survey period, 9.8% of children, or approximately 315 children, experienced food insufficiency.
Because the Household Pulse Survey does not provide data at the county level, we use a model to estimate county-level food insufficiency.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Riverside County</title>
      <link>/riverside/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/riverside/</guid>
      <description>Food insufficiency Unemployment Food insufficiency In the most recent survey period that ended December 19, an estimated 10.8% of Riverside County adults, or approximately 176,000 adults, lived in households experiencing food insufficiency.
Using a model based upon data from the Food Security Supplement of the Current Population Survey, we estimate that in the most recent survey period, 9.1% of children, or approximately 54,900 children, experienced food insufficiency.
Because the Household Pulse Survey does not provide data at the county level, we use a model to estimate county-level food insufficiency.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sacramento County</title>
      <link>/sacramento/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/sacramento/</guid>
      <description>Food insufficiency Unemployment Food insufficiency In the most recent survey period that ended December 19, an estimated 9.7% of Sacramento County adults, or approximately 102,000 adults, lived in households experiencing food insufficiency.
Using a model based upon data from the Food Security Supplement of the Current Population Survey, we estimate that in the most recent survey period, 8.4% of children, or approximately 29,900 children, experienced food insufficiency.
Because the Household Pulse Survey does not provide data at the county level, we use a model to estimate county-level food insufficiency.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>San Benito County</title>
      <link>/san-benito/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/san-benito/</guid>
      <description>Food insufficiency Unemployment Food insufficiency In the most recent survey period that ended December 19, an estimated 13.5% of San Benito County adults, or approximately 5,570 adults, lived in households experiencing food insufficiency.
Using a model based upon data from the Food Security Supplement of the Current Population Survey, we estimate that in the most recent survey period, 11.1% of children, or approximately 1,730 children, experienced food insufficiency.
Because the Household Pulse Survey does not provide data at the county level, we use a model to estimate county-level food insufficiency.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>San Bernardino County</title>
      <link>/san-bernardino/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/san-bernardino/</guid>
      <description>Food insufficiency Unemployment Food insufficiency In the most recent survey period that ended December 19, an estimated 10.6% of San Bernardino County adults, or approximately 151,000 adults, lived in households experiencing food insufficiency.
Using a model based upon data from the Food Security Supplement of the Current Population Survey, we estimate that in the most recent survey period, 9.1% of children, or approximately 50,500 children, experienced food insufficiency.
Because the Household Pulse Survey does not provide data at the county level, we use a model to estimate county-level food insufficiency.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>San Diego County</title>
      <link>/san-diego/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/san-diego/</guid>
      <description>Food insufficiency Unemployment Food insufficiency In the most recent survey period that ended December 19, an estimated 8.1% of San Diego County adults, or approximately 188,000 adults, lived in households experiencing food insufficiency.
Using a model based upon data from the Food Security Supplement of the Current Population Survey, we estimate that in the most recent survey period, 7.3% of children, or approximately 51,000 children, experienced food insufficiency.
Because the Household Pulse Survey does not provide data at the county level, we use a model to estimate county-level food insufficiency.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>San Francisco County</title>
      <link>/san-francisco/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/san-francisco/</guid>
      <description>Food insufficiency Unemployment Food insufficiency In the most recent survey period that ended December 19, an estimated 7.0% of San Francisco County adults, or approximately 47,000 adults, lived in households experiencing food insufficiency.
Using a model based upon data from the Food Security Supplement of the Current Population Survey, we estimate that in the most recent survey period, 6.5% of children, or approximately 7,490 children, experienced food insufficiency.
Because the Household Pulse Survey does not provide data at the county level, we use a model to estimate county-level food insufficiency.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>San Joaquin County</title>
      <link>/san-joaquin/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/san-joaquin/</guid>
      <description>Food insufficiency Unemployment Food insufficiency In the most recent survey period that ended December 19, an estimated 13.5% of San Joaquin County adults, or approximately 66,200 adults, lived in households experiencing food insufficiency.
Using a model based upon data from the Food Security Supplement of the Current Population Survey, we estimate that in the most recent survey period, 11.1% of children, or approximately 22,100 children, experienced food insufficiency.
Because the Household Pulse Survey does not provide data at the county level, we use a model to estimate county-level food insufficiency.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>San Luis Obispo County</title>
      <link>/san-luis-obispo/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/san-luis-obispo/</guid>
      <description>Food insufficiency Unemployment Food insufficiency In the most recent survey period that ended December 19, an estimated 6.5% of San Luis Obispo County adults, or approximately 13,400 adults, lived in households experiencing food insufficiency.
Using a model based upon data from the Food Security Supplement of the Current Population Survey, we estimate that in the most recent survey period, 6.2% of children, or approximately 2,980 children, experienced food insufficiency.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>San Mateo County</title>
      <link>/san-mateo/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/san-mateo/</guid>
      <description>Food insufficiency Unemployment Food insufficiency In the most recent survey period that ended December 19, an estimated 6.5% of San Mateo County adults, or approximately 35,000 adults, lived in households experiencing food insufficiency.
Using a model based upon data from the Food Security Supplement of the Current Population Survey, we estimate that in the most recent survey period, 6.1% of children, or approximately 9,320 children, experienced food insufficiency.
Because the Household Pulse Survey does not provide data at the county level, we use a model to estimate county-level food insufficiency.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Santa Barbara County</title>
      <link>/santa-barbara/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/santa-barbara/</guid>
      <description>Food insufficiency Unemployment Food insufficiency In the most recent survey period that ended December 19, an estimated 8.2% of Santa Barbara County adults, or approximately 25,200 adults, lived in households experiencing food insufficiency.
Using a model based upon data from the Food Security Supplement of the Current Population Survey, we estimate that in the most recent survey period, 7.4% of children, or approximately 7,090 children, experienced food insufficiency.
Because the Household Pulse Survey does not provide data at the county level, we use a model to estimate county-level food insufficiency.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Santa Clara County</title>
      <link>/santa-clara/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/santa-clara/</guid>
      <description>Food insufficiency Unemployment Food insufficiency In the most recent survey period that ended December 19, an estimated 6.6% of Santa Clara County adults, or approximately 88,500 adults, lived in households experiencing food insufficiency.
Using a model based upon data from the Food Security Supplement of the Current Population Survey, we estimate that in the most recent survey period, 6.2% of children, or approximately 25,400 children, experienced food insufficiency.
Because the Household Pulse Survey does not provide data at the county level, we use a model to estimate county-level food insufficiency.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Santa Cruz County</title>
      <link>/santa-cruz/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/santa-cruz/</guid>
      <description>Food insufficiency Unemployment Food insufficiency In the most recent survey period that ended December 19, an estimated 10.8% of Santa Cruz County adults, or approximately 21,100 adults, lived in households experiencing food insufficiency.
Using a model based upon data from the Food Security Supplement of the Current Population Survey, we estimate that in the most recent survey period, 9.2% of children, or approximately 4,660 children, experienced food insufficiency.
Because the Household Pulse Survey does not provide data at the county level, we use a model to estimate county-level food insufficiency.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shasta County</title>
      <link>/shasta/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/shasta/</guid>
      <description>Food insufficiency Unemployment Food insufficiency In the most recent survey period that ended December 19, an estimated 9.2% of Shasta County adults, or approximately 11,400 adults, lived in households experiencing food insufficiency.
Using a model based upon data from the Food Security Supplement of the Current Population Survey, we estimate that in the most recent survey period, 8.0% of children, or approximately 3,050 children, experienced food insufficiency.
Because the Household Pulse Survey does not provide data at the county level, we use a model to estimate county-level food insufficiency.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sierra County</title>
      <link>/sierra/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/sierra/</guid>
      <description>Food insufficiency Unemployment Food insufficiency In the most recent survey period that ended December 19, an estimated 6.9% of Sierra County adults, or approximately 153 adults, lived in households experiencing food insufficiency.
Using a model based upon data from the Food Security Supplement of the Current Population Survey, we estimate that in the most recent survey period, 6.4% of children, or approximately 31 children, experienced food insufficiency.
Because the Household Pulse Survey does not provide data at the county level, we use a model to estimate county-level food insufficiency.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Siskiyou County</title>
      <link>/siskiyou/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/siskiyou/</guid>
      <description>Food insufficiency Unemployment Food insufficiency In the most recent survey period that ended December 19, an estimated 10.0% of Siskiyou County adults, or approximately 3,080 adults, lived in households experiencing food insufficiency.
Using a model based upon data from the Food Security Supplement of the Current Population Survey, we estimate that in the most recent survey period, 8.6% of children, or approximately 738 children, experienced food insufficiency.
Because the Household Pulse Survey does not provide data at the county level, we use a model to estimate county-level food insufficiency.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Solano County</title>
      <link>/solano/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/solano/</guid>
      <description>Food insufficiency Unemployment Food insufficiency In the most recent survey period that ended December 19, an estimated 9.9% of Solano County adults, or approximately 30,400 adults, lived in households experiencing food insufficiency.
Using a model based upon data from the Food Security Supplement of the Current Population Survey, we estimate that in the most recent survey period, 8.5% of children, or approximately 8,200 children, experienced food insufficiency.
Because the Household Pulse Survey does not provide data at the county level, we use a model to estimate county-level food insufficiency.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sonoma County</title>
      <link>/sonoma/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/sonoma/</guid>
      <description>Food insufficiency Unemployment Food insufficiency In the most recent survey period that ended December 19, an estimated 7.2% of Sonoma County adults, or approximately 25,300 adults, lived in households experiencing food insufficiency.
Using a model based upon data from the Food Security Supplement of the Current Population Survey, we estimate that in the most recent survey period, 6.6% of children, or approximately 6,190 children, experienced food insufficiency.
Because the Household Pulse Survey does not provide data at the county level, we use a model to estimate county-level food insufficiency.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stanislaus County</title>
      <link>/stanislaus/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stanislaus/</guid>
      <description>Food insufficiency Unemployment Food insufficiency In the most recent survey period that ended December 19, an estimated 13.2% of Stanislaus County adults, or approximately 47,000 adults, lived in households experiencing food insufficiency.
Using a model based upon data from the Food Security Supplement of the Current Population Survey, we estimate that in the most recent survey period, 10.9% of children, or approximately 15,800 children, experienced food insufficiency.
Because the Household Pulse Survey does not provide data at the county level, we use a model to estimate county-level food insufficiency.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sutter County</title>
      <link>/sutter/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/sutter/</guid>
      <description>Food insufficiency Unemployment Food insufficiency In the most recent survey period that ended December 19, an estimated 16.7% of Sutter County adults, or approximately 10,600 adults, lived in households experiencing food insufficiency.
Using a model based upon data from the Food Security Supplement of the Current Population Survey, we estimate that in the most recent survey period, 13.3% of children, or approximately 3,260 children, experienced food insufficiency.
Because the Household Pulse Survey does not provide data at the county level, we use a model to estimate county-level food insufficiency.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tehama County</title>
      <link>/tehama/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/tehama/</guid>
      <description>Food insufficiency Unemployment Food insufficiency In the most recent survey period that ended December 19, an estimated 9.7% of Tehama County adults, or approximately 4,260 adults, lived in households experiencing food insufficiency.
Using a model based upon data from the Food Security Supplement of the Current Population Survey, we estimate that in the most recent survey period, 8.4% of children, or approximately 1,270 children, experienced food insufficiency.
Because the Household Pulse Survey does not provide data at the county level, we use a model to estimate county-level food insufficiency.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Trinity County</title>
      <link>/trinity/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/trinity/</guid>
      <description>Food insufficiency Unemployment Food insufficiency In the most recent survey period that ended December 19, an estimated 8.2% of Trinity County adults, or approximately 733 adults, lived in households experiencing food insufficiency.
Using a model based upon data from the Food Security Supplement of the Current Population Survey, we estimate that in the most recent survey period, 7.3% of children, or approximately 153 children, experienced food insufficiency.
Because the Household Pulse Survey does not provide data at the county level, we use a model to estimate county-level food insufficiency.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tulare County</title>
      <link>/tulare/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/tulare/</guid>
      <description>Food insufficiency Unemployment Food insufficiency In the most recent survey period that ended December 19, an estimated 21.7% of Tulare County adults, or approximately 62,000 adults, lived in households experiencing food insufficiency.
Using a model based upon data from the Food Security Supplement of the Current Population Survey, we estimate that in the most recent survey period, 16.9% of children, or approximately 23,500 children, experienced food insufficiency.
Because the Household Pulse Survey does not provide data at the county level, we use a model to estimate county-level food insufficiency.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tuolumne County</title>
      <link>/tuolumne/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/tuolumne/</guid>
      <description>Food insufficiency Unemployment Food insufficiency In the most recent survey period that ended December 19, an estimated 7.6% of Tuolumne County adults, or approximately 3,020 adults, lived in households experiencing food insufficiency.
Using a model based upon data from the Food Security Supplement of the Current Population Survey, we estimate that in the most recent survey period, 6.9% of children, or approximately 617 children, experienced food insufficiency.
Because the Household Pulse Survey does not provide data at the county level, we use a model to estimate county-level food insufficiency.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ventura County</title>
      <link>/ventura/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/ventura/</guid>
      <description>Food insufficiency Unemployment Food insufficiency In the most recent survey period that ended December 19, an estimated 9.3% of Ventura County adults, or approximately 53,900 adults, lived in households experiencing food insufficiency.
Using a model based upon data from the Food Security Supplement of the Current Population Survey, we estimate that in the most recent survey period, 8.1% of children, or approximately 15,200 children, experienced food insufficiency.
Because the Household Pulse Survey does not provide data at the county level, we use a model to estimate county-level food insufficiency.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Yolo County</title>
      <link>/yolo/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/yolo/</guid>
      <description>Food insufficiency Unemployment Food insufficiency In the most recent survey period that ended December 19, an estimated 9.5% of Yolo County adults, or approximately 14,700 adults, lived in households experiencing food insufficiency.
Using a model based upon data from the Food Security Supplement of the Current Population Survey, we estimate that in the most recent survey period, 8.3% of children, or approximately 3,710 children, experienced food insufficiency.
Because the Household Pulse Survey does not provide data at the county level, we use a model to estimate county-level food insufficiency.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Yuba County</title>
      <link>/yuba/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/yuba/</guid>
      <description>Food insufficiency Unemployment Food insufficiency In the most recent survey period that ended December 19, an estimated 12.4% of Yuba County adults, or approximately 6,250 adults, lived in households experiencing food insufficiency.
Using a model based upon data from the Food Security Supplement of the Current Population Survey, we estimate that in the most recent survey period, 10.3% of children, or approximately 2,180 children, experienced food insufficiency.
Because the Household Pulse Survey does not provide data at the county level, we use a model to estimate county-level food insufficiency.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
